[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
happy Sabbath and welcome to the living
Mana Seventh-day Adventist Church we are
so happy that you are here with us we
are excited about uh the the topic that
we have for Sabbath school today I know
it's going to be a blessing to many of
you uh just learning about what some
Ministries are doing to really reach the
people those people that are in need and
then we and that they are really truly
being the hands and feet of Jesus and
not only are we going to learn about
what they're doing but uh by God's grace
it's going to inspire all of us to do
this work as well because this is what
God has called us to do so we just want
to welcome all of you again let us know
where you're watching from before we
went
um live I guess I saw that somebody was
watching from Berlin
um in Germany and so that was the first
time I've seen not Germany but Berlin
you know specifically so welcome
um I see Toronto Canada yeah please put
in the chat where you're watching from
because we are just so happy that you
are that you are here with us Los
Angeles welcome New Jersey
it's another one from uh that's our Rick
from Canada of course
Rick and Julie are are here uh brother
Sean always wonderful to to see you on
here and to and to hear your voice he's
like that that energy
um that like that just that really live
energy of living Mana church we really
appreciate it Collegedale Tennessee not
too far from us Walla Walla Washington
welcome we are so happy to see each and
every one of you uh we want you to
before I forget because I feel like I
forgot last week I want to let you guys
know that if you have prayer requests
we want you to put it in the chat
because our prayer team is um they're
they're here they are recording your
prayer requests brother Terry will be
praying over many of them
um in the Divine hour during our church
service so please put your prayer
request in the chat also after the
sermon today we have
um an Afterglow which is an altar live
and I have to tell you this is where we
really connect as the living man of
church this is where we get to know each
other hear each other's voices we can
even see each other's faces you can do
live video but for those who don't want
it
share your voice share your face you
don't have to do that you can just
listen to the prayers to the testimonies
to the prayer requests that are being
shared there that is where you share
like what the service meant to you what
you learned during this sabbatical time
what you learned
um in the sermon or throughout today's
worship service and so just it is truly
a blessing to just be able to come
together and connect there so if you
have not downloaded altar live you can
do that that is in the chat I saw it
earlier but I think we can put it back
in there now so it can be fresh in the
feed and so you can download alter live
and then right after the sermon you can
be a part of that and so we just really
welcome you to participate in that
because it really is truly where we
build community here at Living manage
Church uh just uh before we go on I just
saw a prayer request that looks urgent
and so I just want to take a moment to
just uh just to pray stop and pray okay
and Gregory Hall so we put it up on the
screen for those of you that are
watching okay uh please just join us in
prayer I'm not exactly sure what the
issue is okay but let's just pray for a
moment heavenly father I want to lift
Gregory Hall to you Lord uh his fiancee
is apparently having trouble breathing
right at this moment Lord I pray we pray
Lord as a church we're praying from
around the world right now yeah that um
you would intercede Lord and and restore
her breath Lord and whatever the
situation is we just ask that you would
uh intervene in that situation right now
Lord and please both give them both
peace and uh and remedy this situation
this is our prayer in Jesus name we ask
it amen amen amen amen amen
yes let's just keep them in prayer as we
are moving forward and this is what we
are we are a church family and so even
though we're online and we're not
directly in each other's faces this is
live this is real this is real life um
this is real Church
um it's just in a different format and
so
um we just you know want you to just
know that we are connected and we care
about all your personal things that
you're going through so just like if you
come to a church and ask for prayer you
can just put in the chat like you know
what like Gregory just did we need
prayer now so let's keep
um them in prayer as as we continue to
worship continue to worship so yes for
those of you who are just joining us I
don't know if we have any first timers
we like to see if there's any
first-timers we know we have
um those who worship with us every week
and we're so thankful and appreciative
of everyone who you know comes into this
space to worship with us but if you are
a first time uh visitor with us today
put a one in the chat that and while
they're they're doing that for all the
everyone else we would like for you to
at this time to share on your social
media the platform that you're that
you're watching on that we're live and
invite people to to worship with us at
this time and we also want to invite you
to follow us on our Instagram my living
Mana um that is also the other way that
we are letting people know that we are
here what our programming is all about
on our Instagram you will find little
clips of different things we have done
from the sermon sermons I should say
that Pastor Myers has preached also
there's uh living Mana I mean sorry not
living Manna but mental health Monday
clips of our the topics that we've
covered there uh because every Monday we
have we're talking about mental health
and then there's uh clips from
um true Health Tuesday with Dr schweltz
and Dr Reynolds
we also have the um clips from Dr Panda
as well and that is on Thursday every
Thursday evening and so we want you to
follow us there share there because it
is that way where you can just share the
Little Clips with your friends with your
co-workers with your family members and
say hey this topic might interest you
this is where I go to church this is
where I worship each and every week and
these type of things that they cover
just to give you an idea so definitely
we want you to follow us on Instagram
that we want you to share with others
and share the things that are on there
that you think may be of interest to to
those who uh you want to invite to the
church and so we're making it really
really easy and I've said before I don't
know how many I don't know if we can
make it any easier to be able to share
and invite people
um to go to church even on Sabbath but
really too we really want you to invite
them to the week what our program that's
going on during the week right because
that is like on practical topics that
can be a blessing to so many we just
finished I mean we did our just finished
our marriage topics here on sap school
but we also just completed that with
relationships and our mental health
Mondays as well and I always say that
the doctors are providing
just a wealth of information that I mean
we all can benefit because we all we're
living in these bodies and because of
sin our bodies you know we get sick we
have disease there's just different
things that happen and they are showing
us you know the best way to keep our
bodies healthy
um and so you definitely want to tune
into that and share that with others as
well amen amen and uh we uh have a
special
yes Sabbath school today
um and I think it's a timely one yes
yeah I think it's a timely one
um
okay all right so yes my
face gone to sleep
so what we're gonna do we're gonna have
to uh probably switch out microphones
here that's fine
okay
all right uh so uh let's go ahead and uh
we're gonna invite uh our guests on
um so let's bring on loami and Eric
um
he just came in and disappeared all
right uh Eric Camarillo right
is your last name cat
you're muted you're muted
so Eric Miller
Camarillo Camarillo yes yes Camarillo
all right
um well welcome man welcome
you've been here before you've spoken us
first before uh attante is saying
welcome for you
um we're gonna this we're gonna do we're
gonna ask both of you to introduce
yourself we're gonna we're gonna switch
out a microphone real quick so if you
guys are just taught to our audience and
kind of let them know a little bit about
your ministry uh the ministry you've
done uh um together and just uh we want
to talk about salt that's why you guys
are here and uh just give a uh like I
said a little introduction and then
we're gonna get into some detail of what
it means to do Outreach in the community
okay
so whichever one you want to go first
um I'll go first um my name is Laramie
Richardson I am an associate speaker for
revelation of Hope Ministries with Taj
paclet uh had the awesome privilege of
working with my brother uh Eric
um for a few years when I was in Orlando
um currently I'm
um started my own non-profit
organization
um entitled The I am greater Foundation
that focuses on providing scholarships
mentoring and tutoring for kids in the
inner city communities that idea sparked
a little bit right before the pandemic
but it started when we did our uh
tutoring and mentoring uh uh classes
um in the neighborhood Eric when we were
uh down in Apopka in the neighboring uh
communities uh offering
uh tutoring services for one of the
neighborhoods that we was working for
and so that passion kind of transitioned
over and so yeah so that's a little bit
about myself and what I'm doing
currently
cool cool uh yeah no it's it's uh yeah
uh loamy and I were actually roommates
for a good a good amount of time too so
we really got to know each other
um yeah my name is Eric Camarillo uh
president for assault Outreach uh
uh you know God inspired the idea back
in 2011 and uh you know it's been about
11 years now we're serving people
experiencing homelessness
um here in downtown Orlando
um and uh yeah no I'm excited to be here
be a part of this so yeah thank you for
thank you for inviting inviting us
we are so happy to have um both of you
hopefully you can you can hear me as you
guys can hear me put it yeah yeah okay
great great and we were successful in
changing that out well we are excited to
to have you
um I have followed personally I've
followed What salt has done I think I
learned about salt in 2018 maybe a
little bit before that but I remember we
met you at the ASI in Orlando
um and I was impressed from day one from
what the ministry
um is doing so let's tell our audience
what the ministry has done because I
don't want to give it away because I can
because I before we do that let's pray
okay yes and then
then I want to talk about the name first
okay why that name okay all right so all
right let's pray and then we'll do that
Heavenly Father we thank you Lord for um
giving us this opportunity Lord to share
um um
about this ministry today Lord and uh
just the timeliness of it Lord we just
ask that you would
um
uh fill us Lord encourage us strengthen
us Lord to do what you called us all to
do and uh bless this this Sabbath school
this morning is our prayer in Jesus name
amen amen amen
so uh let's talk about the name
yeah
so when we so it was back in 2011 I had
just become an Adventist Christian it
was about a year year after becoming an
Adventist Christian and um
you know a series of events happened
um that I believe God was using to
really
um solidify my faith and
um you know he inspired the idea of four
salt which was really initially to get
young adults together to do practical
and impactful consistent Outreach in the
community and uh so me and three friends
we we got together and we literally were
in my friend's room and we prayed all
night it was three of us and we're like
God what do you want to call this thing
and uh and one of the names was was salt
and the acronym was service and love
together now salt comes from Matthew 5
13 you know that we are the salt of the
earth right and uh and you know the
acronyms service and love together I I
we felt like at that time we saw a lot
of service
without love and when I say service
without love I mean going to go and and
feed people experiencing homelessness
but hanging back behind the tables and
not actually engaging with them and
loving on them and interacting with them
and and we see a lot of quote unquote
love but without service right people
that say I love people but then they
don't go and actually act on that love
and we felt like the combination of the
two really exemplified what Jesus
defined as what being the salt of the
earth is and bringing the two together
to really um uh exemplify just two
crisis you know and and what the Bible
the Bible says he is so yeah
yes all right
um
I think that's I think that's uh
I think that's a powerful
thought it's a powerful approach I think
that like action with no love yeah I
mean it's easy to say love
mm-hmm
without action
right and I'm being love without action
is not really love right exactly exactly
right it's not really love so
um salt you are the light of the world
you are the salt of the earth
right right
um and if the salt loses
its purpose then it's good for nothing
right exactly yeah for and for salt to
really have an effect on anybody
it has to be mingled with that thing
right it has to be intimately mingled
and yeah I think that that's a huge huge
core uh uh core of who salt is is that
we want to make sure that we're creating
relationship with people yeah and you
know we we studied some data recently
which is which is crazy and I I hope
that we can get this data out more is we
so from August of 2020 through uh March
of 2022
um salt was involved in helping to end
homelessness for over a thousand people
over 50 percent of those people were
visiting us two or three times a week
and as their frequency of visits went
down so did successful housing outcomes
so so what that told us was the deeper
relationship we have with someone the
more likely they're going to succeed
right and to move forward
um and so that that was a that was a key
finding I think it you know kind of uh
really represents a core value of like
who we are yeah yeah
so you're yeah you're do you're
doing and not just saying right yeah
amen yeah
tell us and tell our viewing audience a
little bit more about the ministry as
far as like I have to say my
favorite highest Sabbath that I've ever
experienced have been when I we've just
done Outreach I think
um goodness that was the a-man
conference I have no idea what year that
was but maybe 2016 and all we like the
entire day from you know like I don't
know 8 A.M to like 6 p.m we were just
serving people all day and that was the
best that's just one example one of the
best sabbaths that I've had in doing
service but you your ministry takes it
further first of all you just don't do
it on Sabbath number one and number two
because people's needs are every day but
number two you don't just stop at that
initial
service you follow up am I correct with
them yeah yeah so we operate uh five
days a week right now
um we have uh you know with God's help
we have about 35 Staff members at the
moment that are serving over 200 people
a day experiencing homelessness
um and you know we offer 12 different
services so you know behind me here you
can uh you can see our shower trailer so
we offer showers through a four bathroom
shower trailer to the unsheltered we
also have a laundry trailer it has six
washers and six dryers in it
um we do charging stations we do we're
doing mail services for over 600 people
right now because they don't have an
address are they in the full Security
checks their food stamp cards you know
that kind of thing
um you know we do haircuts we do case
management uh and we do mental health
counseling so there's a a 12 total
different Services we offer and we also
have Outreach pastors a part of the
organization so starting last year in
March we hired our first Outreach pastor
and we hired and he graduated from
Oakwood University we hired another
Outreach pastor this past January
because the need was continuing to grow
shout out to Wilfredo
it was our first Outreach Pastor uh in
March and and Joffrey Saint Hilaire was
our second and uh they do church service
on site because a lot of our friends do
not feel comfortable going into churches
right right you know what they're
experiencing and and also unfortunately
many of the local churches
um you know there are some local
churches that that do not feel
comfortable know how to handle someone
experiencing homelessness in their
congregation don't come here
we all come here we we don't have money
we're not giving you my like yeah there
are then there are some locally that
that really know how to really engage
with them and help them and Empower them
to take the next step but then there are
others that maybe are not so sure on how
to do that
um you know so they also do group Bible
studies four times a week um they were
doing it once a week but they begged for
more and more Bible studies so we we
went ahead and we're doing it four times
a week now
um and then they also do one-on-one like
kind of spiritual counseling kind of
acting as a Chaplain for them because
when you're experiencing homelessness
it's hard to process that it's hard to
process like
you know always that question well why
is why did God let this happen to me you
know and and they kind of helped them
guide them through that process and once
a year we do calls for baptism as well
um just to give them the opportunity to
be baptized when we first did our
baptisms last year
um there were tears um and they were
like you mean you mean I can get
baptized and and our pastor was like
yeah yeah you can be baptized if you if
you really wanted and it was just such
an emotional time so so yeah that's
that's another element of the
organization too
so Tom are you so I have so many
questions here but are you first of all
how are you funded and second are you
working like with the local County like
you said case management so
are you working with the county so we
have we have our we we are getting uh
some funding from local government
um we we all we our case managers are
all our you know they're our staff so
um you know they uh uh as far as the
case management goes they do a full
assessment they figure out what the
needs are then they refer them out to
other organizations we kind of act as
that front door refer them out to other
organizations that could help them take
the next step and then they go ahead and
uh uh if there isn't an organization
that could help them or if there's a
long waiting list then we'll go ahead
and uh find a creative way to meet that
need ourselves
um but we starting in 2020 when covet
hit was when we started the first get
some funding from local government so
city of Orlando uh you have we're here
in Orlando Florida so city of Orlando
has given some funding toward this and
Orange County the county we're in has
given some funding toward it and we
gotten some funny from DCF and things
like that so so we have about and you
asked about funding so about 50 of our
funding is coming from local government
we're on the we're in the process of of
decreasing that over time
um yeah and the rest of our funding
comes from individuals
um you know like just to give you an
example last year we raised about a
million 1.4 million
um
fifth uh about uh 600 000 came from
local government 372
000 came from actually Adventists
Adventist business owners individuals or
or foundations and the rest just came
from other sources you know we've had
some Sunday churches and some other
groups of people from other
denominations
um and individuals give toward us so
yeah it's been great to see everyone
come together for this kind of work so
yeah yeah I I I have to I have to share
this because it's so yeah
no no listen so so because of the work
that Eric and the volunteers and
everybody who's poured into the city of
Orlando can you uh tell them Eric uh the
city of Orlando acknowledge salt on what
day oh yeah yeah so so on uh on April uh
so we launched our laundry trailer on
April 15th of 2021 and we invite we did
a rip we want to do a ribbon cutting so
we invited the mayor the City
commissioners came out we had some other
local government leaders um come out as
well and some other people and uh you
know we did the ribbon cutting it was it
was cool it was a blessing and at the
end of it the mayor surprised us and he
made a proclamation to call every April
15th salt day in the city of Orlando Oh
amen that's amazing it's my mom's
birthday yeah oh wow okay okay
anymore I guess no that's amazing that's
awesome that's awesome so
um because you said 50 of the funding
comes from local government but are you
you're still considered a non-profit
organization okay so yeah I know this is
we're not at the end but I think we
could mention it now and then again at
the end if people want to to give and to
support this ministry how do they do
that yeah so they can go to uh salt
outreach.org
and and you know give toward there
um there's also a text number they can
text somersault s-u-m-m-e-r salt so
um we're actually getting a triple
there's a triple match happening right
now so every dollar donated is actually
equaling three dollars at the moment
till the end of September
um and uh and yeah and and on the
website there'll be other ways that they
can see how they can give and contribute
and be a part and of course always
looking for volunteers we have 500
volunteers last year give about 5 000
hours so it's a key part of what we do
yeah wow
what was your involvement in the
ministry and how did you know
how did you all get together and yeah so
um prior I moved back down to to Orlando
and
um Eric and I met I think we was no
actually was doing an ay at one of the
local churches there and uh we ate at
Taco Bell that's originally where where
we connected
um
yeah so this you know salt was still
kind of
um
uh still in the process of what what it
is now you know it's been a lot of work
that's gone into it so anyway long story
short I was an Outreach coordinator so
uh part of my responsibilities was the
code to various churches shared the
vision of salt try to work that church
partnership with with salt and try to
get volunteers from the church to you
know to help out and and try to really
Implement salt into every church that we
can get into right and so how you know a
lot of people don't know how and so
um that was kind of my responsibility
and then I um from there we uh
transitioned
um I'll never forget I was taking a nap
because Eric and I was roommates for a
few years and um you're like hey man we
have this great idea you know you work
with with kids and I know you have a
passion for it why won't you uh uh spare
you know head out on and do a um a
tutoring program for one of the
neighborhoods that that we work at and
so that was another responsibility and
it was just so awesome to be able to go
and visit these kids man and
um just being able to connect and that
kind of Splendid the seed for me as I
you know transition out of Orlando and
and and continue to
um go in the direction that God was
leading me to start my own non-profit to
really help inner city Youth and
mentoring and providing scholarships and
and all of those things but it was
started with salt and and seeing the
impact we was making in the city of
Orlando and uh really just trying to
share the vision to as many churches we
went to ASI when we pulled up and uh we
didn't they just finished the shower
trailer yeah they like us before ASI
actually pastor Pastor Myers we were
doing some interviews that day I think
you recorded a little video for us
so that that's that was my involvement
with salt and so man just to see where
it's at just you know to where it's at
to what it's doing now is it's been
phenomenal to see and so he's been
inspiring a lot of people's like how can
we start a assault in our community hey
can we do assault here and there so they
know I was associated with them and so
I'm always
referring them right back to Salt
Outreach man you know so what started
off as a need and Eric experiencing he
has a phenomenal testimony as well of
his experience with hopelessness is what
started this whole idea and and to see
what he needed and now providing that
need for others who experience the same
thing it's been awesome to see really
has well no well I mean that's a good
segue because Eric tell us about your
experience because I think sharing your
experience will go into my next question
was going to be
um helping
other Christians who
um want to help and to work with this
community but don't really know how or
what to say or how to interact because
you had mentioned that earlier so tell
us your story and then how you think
um is the best way to encourage other
people and how they can interact and
help people in the in the end that are
in need yeah where did you where did you
go to school to learn how to do this so
I I I uh
um I studied social work
um at this at University of Central
Florida got my bachelor's there I got my
Master's in nonprofit management from
that same school
um and then I I got some certifications
so I got a certification as a as a CMP
so a certified non-profit professional
and then a cfre which is certified
fundraising executive
um and so that all I I was working in HR
during all that time and I was kind of
moving up in the ranks in the HR world
and uh but I I knew and and this I would
encourage anyone if you're going to
school
don't go to school for something that
isn't going to be your calling you know
what I'm saying I think a lot of time
like oh well I'm gonna you know I'm
doing this ministry on the side but let
me go to school for what my job is in
and I I don't think that's
I I don't think that's a good use of our
of our education I I would say go to
school for for the ministry that you're
a part of you know that will help that
Ministry
um but to answer your question uh
attante um I I uh my testimony is long
I've gone through a lot of weird strange
stuff
um and one day maybe I'll get to share
it all but I did experience homelessness
um before becoming a Christian when I
was 20 years old I was uh
habit I I was very I was in a different
world back then uh and I I just all I
cared about was was money and and and
success and and that's kind of what what
my God was and uh I went up there to try
and start a business and it didn't work
out
I had money basically for two weeks and
I was I was up there in Chicago for six
months in a car in my car and uh out to
eat to eat meals I would go to a Mexican
restaurant you know how to give the
chips and salsa before your meal I'd go
in eat the chips and salsa and then walk
out and I would go to 7-Eleven bathrooms
and clean up use the bathroom there
um I would if I had some money I'd with
the dollar I'd buy a piece of bread from
Panera Bread rip it in half it's my
breakfast and dinner get a bunch of
butter free butter from them pile it up
and that would be what I would eat for
my my meals so I know what it's like um
to not have access to your basic needs
on experiencing homelessness
um and I think that is one of the drives
that has helped to inspire
um this type of work you know
um
so yeah that's that's been a blessing
and then you asked about how people can
help someone experiencing homelessness
yeah and how did and like like I mean
just through your
earrings right so if someone was
go let's just say you did stumble upon
I don't know a church or a group of
Christians or whatever how should how
how should they have interacted like
what is the way that you feel is the
most appropriate appropriate way to
interact with those who are in that
space
yeah so
um I get a lot of phone calls from
people
um you know people that genuinely want
to help people experiencing homelessness
and we also get a lot of phone calls
from churches too so when it comes to
people
um what I would say is before you you uh
because it's so easy
um to be working with someone
experiencing homelessness and for that
to totally almost make you homeless you
know what I mean because you you just
the need is so great you know and you
only have such limited resources the
first thing I would do is to pray and
ask God God I want to help this person
but what is my limit
so God might tell you my limit's 500
bucks okay so you know once you get to
that 500 range maybe you're buying meals
maybe you helped with the hotel one
night whatever it is once you hit that
500 range and more is being asked of you
you just say hey I I can't I can't do it
you know because you know your limit
that you set with god um and then
obviously trying to get them linked to
an organization that can help that
um the church is now um we actually
created some programs for churches where
we actually can coach and Empower and
equip the church to duplicate what we're
doing in Orlando in their Community
um so so and then we also have a program
we can provide ongoing kind of
Consulting for that church to help them
duplicate this model we believe this
model is effective um it's proven to be
effective here in Orlando and we we our
vision is that every metropolitan area
has a drop-in center for people
experiencing homelessness even if it's
not even if it's not us providing that
drop-in center service if it's somebody
then that's that's okay because then
everyone experiencing homelessness in
every metropolitan area will get their
basic needs met which I believe is truly
showing Christ's love to these people
and opening that door to to take things
to even you know greater Heights you
know what I mean so yeah let me let me
ask you this
um and either one of you can answer this
but
so you know this is an online church we
don't have a church building but we have
members that are all around the world
yes
so
um
this whole Vision Eric started with you
right one individual who said hey let me
let me see what I can do in helping you
know people that are that are in need
um if
some of our members some of our people
wanted to start this in their area and
they may not be connected with the
church right right like man I could
I could fear had something like this
in my area do you the salt currently
provide
that kind of training where it's more of
more for individuals right versus a
church training uh yeah Church training
like yeah yeah I see what you're saying
we don't have a a model like that right
now and the reason the reason why
is because now I I do think there can be
an individual that says yes I believe
with God's help I can duplicate this in
my city and that's and that's that's
that's the first step right right The
Next Step would be finding a team
because it it you know on their own they
won't be there's only so far you can go
so if if there's a group of people that
maybe are in an area that say we want to
duplicate this you know then then that
will be um that will be key and then if
that's there then we can go ahead and
and kind of uh mimic what we would do
with churches but for this group if that
makes sense yeah so Eric let me let me
let me ask both of you this again when
you started the ministry did you start
it connected to a church or did you
start it
with that small group of people
we did start it uh connected with a
church at first so now we we I was I was
uh I was the president of the youth or
whatever for one a church a local church
and it was two of my other leaders that
we got together and and had this vision
and and kind of you know started to to
do this but it was too it a church could
not contain could not properly manage
the ministry because it's it's to the uh
it's too it's just too big you know I
don't know if that makes sense or not
but it's just yeah yeah it's too much so
so we had to separate from the church
and and create a separate 501c3
non-profit organization that's a
supporting Ministry of the church you
know we're part of ASI right against my
Ministry but but um so yeah I I don't
think it needs to start out of a church
if that makes sense it just so happened
that we did but that was because it was
just the beginning you know what I mean
yeah I do I do want to bring up a point
because Eric by the time you've got
you didn't just go out there serving
food right randomly There Was You did
surveys and things of that nature right
to see what was the greatest need in the
places that you were servicing am I am I
correct in that yeah yeah so so survey
so we we just we started with food with
before the surveys we started with food
but that was just to initially gather
people together because food is is
something that can really bring people
together then we started to do the
surveys yeah and the surveys is what led
to everything everything that salt is
right now led from us asking the people
that are ourselves what is it that you
need and then we we continue to to to oh
you need this okay A year later shower
trailer oh you need this year later you
know two years later a laundry trailer
so so that's kind of what
helped to grow the ministry and we we
aren't you know we're not like
you know we what we would encourage
other people to do is we would teach
them from based on our experience based
on what we've gone through just without
all of the the mistakes that we made you
know right
um so we would probably we would
encourage that same yeah we would
encourage that same thing as doing the
surveys to figure out where's the best
place to start yeah I love that you
asked them what they need because we are
we tend to automatically go to
um okay let's feed them they need food
which you know many do but
um we actually did uh some Ministry
um this was in the Bay area and we you
know visited the homeless shelter and
they were saying look what we need
um is more of like fresh undergarments
and things like that that's what they
were saying at that time
um and and so you know we cut we we made
gift bags that were geared to what they
were saying but I I mean I like it that
you did the surveys
um just to see because there's there's a
lot of re I don't say a lot but there's
resources where they can get food but
they can't get other things yeah yeah
it's it's important even to interview
and tour the local organizations to see
for yourself maybe you know there was an
organization close to us that was
offering Towers but they only had
um four showers they were they were not
well kept so a lot of people did not
like to go and take showers there and
they only were open four hours a day
five days a week and they were only
showering 30 people we're showering 80
people right now at 70 to 80 people a
day so they they didn't even have the
capacity to fill that needs so how many
trucks how many uh how many sour
[Music]
um
of I don't know are they trucks trailers
they're trailers yeah all right how many
of them do you have so we have one
shower trailer right now we have a
clothing trailer and a laundry trailer
uh we have a storage bus
and uh we have we we also have a second
trailer coming that's what should we get
before the end of the year so okay
do people do people just come like they
just like how does it work how do they
they it's it's mobile so that it moves
is that what you do you go to certain
areas and they know do they sign up to
say to say okay I'm gonna be there on
this time this day I don't know how do
you do it yeah we did rotate a lot in
the beginning
um because there's such a great need
where we are right now we're stationed
at our downtown location five days a
week and then we go on our on on another
day we go once a week to another area
and another day we rotate other cities
um and so when they come we register
them for all the services they need for
that day and we get them in queue for
those Services
um and then we call them up to our
check-in window which will then get them
to you know then send them off to those
Services when it's their turn right
I just absolutely love this yeah I mean
it's a great idea and it's so exciting
yeah and we don't you know we're so
we're at a place in uh with our church
where we want to encourage people as I
said our church is global so we've got
people in all kinds of different places
we want to start encouraging our members
and even those that are not our members
are Faith members we call them yeah they
got their local membership where they
are so they're not officially members of
of our church but they still watch but
we want to encourage people to
have that you know
ministerial
entrepreneurial Spirit right where it's
like okay what can I do in my area I got
five people in my area that you know all
part of living matter or two people or
three people
my my you know so we want people to
start getting active
and in fact we we're looking at you know
dedicating one week out of the month and
we're working on this talking about it
inspired by
evangelist Richardson yeah so he became
preached a sermon how long ago uh it's
probably about a month ago yeah okay and
your message was about you know being a
you know getting out of our comfort zone
basically and really as as atante says
be the hands and feet of Jesus and and I
want to say into our and to all of our
our viewers and members and and our
guest members and all our lovely
followers you know here at at Living
Mana we we try to provide so much
um good Bible teaching messages
practical learning all throughout the
week and I was telling my husband I was
like our members are quite full
they are probably have they're very very
full and they need to exercise some of
that you know and it's it's it's time
for us to to begin to go out there into
the world and be the salt
um of the earth as well I do want to say
one thing because I know as a church as
a collective there's
um a lot of young people are leaving
right they they don't really feel the
importance of church and one of the
things that was a huge draw of salt was
a lot of our volunteers were kind of not
engaged in the church and Erica you can
share more on this us well how many of
the volunteers that started off
volunteering ended up being baptized
recommitted and then reconnecting back
to the church because of salt yeah so
when we started
um we we had 40 volunteer leaders I mean
they were we we tried to split up the
work as much as possible because we're
all students and working and doing other
things you know so um 20 uh half of
those volunteer leaders were all
backslid Adventists that came back to
the church
um uh through through service through
Outreach and through something you know
um like this something very practical
and I think I think that's what our Our
Generation and generations of you know
after us are looking for they're looking
for ways to get involved and and to see
the church making an impactful
measurable difference in the community
and yeah I'm about to see
I I think one of the reasons why I think
a lot of people and young people
particularly leave the church not the
only reason but one of the reasons is
because the church talks a lot and does
a does little right so when when people
see that
that
we're not
actually doing what we're what we say
love your neighbor yeah I'm not gonna
love my neighbor I mean I want to kind
of transition into uh salt Ministry
helping some
um some immigrants right before I even
go yeah yeah yeah before I go right
there I just want to say you know I
talked about the ministry that we've
done in service it's been my by far my
most enjoyable Sabbath of my entire life
but also for our kids our teenage kids
like they like
yeah they just they love it they love it
I mean they're young adults now are you
know in college now but they absolutely
like their their mindset just changes
when we're doing service especially on
Sabbath and helping other people like so
I agree that that's what young people
are looking for because and I think when
the world sees
sometimes the hypocrisy
they're like why would I want
what you have you know why wouldn't when
when
you know when Christians are celebrating
the the
ill treatment
of
people trying to find Refuge right
how do we look the world in the face
and say yeah God is love right
how do how do we do that
um and you know we're getting to the
place now where
and I'm about I'm about to free I'll let
you know
I'm about to preach about this the the
sermon coming up
is about to be
yeah
how can you claim to love God when you
don't love your neighbor God who you
can't see when you don't love your
neighbor who you can see
um
and Eric tell us about so that Ivor can
like not preach a sermon right yet but
not quite yet but tell us about what
Saul is doing with that like with
um immigrants who you find that are in
in need of of your services as well so
so we've seen a different refugees come
through
um you know from different countries we
have a Syrian family and that and as
well and that kind of thing but we we
have recently been seeing a huge influx
in the past two months of Venezuelan
refugees
um and their stories are all all very
similar they've walked over 20 2500
miles from Venezuela with their family
across the Mexican border
turn themselves over to ice then get
driven to another state just to get
driven to another state and these people
when they finally get to us and and
praise God they find us because I like
there was there was a group of five that
were literally wandering around in one
of the nice neighborhoods here in
Orlando and they didn't know what to do
they were just dropped off in a random
place and just they didn't know English
you know they were just trying to figure
out what to do you know and someone had
found them and called us and we went to
go pick them up
but um you know some of them hadn't
showered in over a month because they
don't have access to a shower some of
them barely have eaten they've lost so
much weight and these and their kids
involved too and and that's that's also
very very heartbreaking so they come to
us for services we give them we are able
to provide those basic needs and
unfortunately there isn't a lot of
resources here in in Central Florida for
these people
um seeking Asylum
um their Asylum dates are not for nine
months so they can't even get uh
anything to work so they literally are
forced they can't make income they're
forced to be homeless and to try and
survive until their Asylum date and you
know we by God's grace you know he's
he's helped our team and our team man
they have such big hearts um we have a a
great amazing team they um they were
able to house 18 of those 20. wow and
find creative ways to get them housed
and off the street and you know there's
even some shelters Unfortunately they
have turned them away because they don't
have IDs you know what I'm saying and
it's like you know we yeah it's it's
been heartbreaking and um heartbreaking
you know it's it's you know but but with
God's help we're we're able to you know
we're able to step into the Gap a little
bit to help with that so wow
I mean you get to preach your sermon so
I get to just say it right now but I'm
just you know just listening to this I
mean it is heartbreaking and for like as
Christians like if we think that God
doesn't care about people
um outside of your border of your
country like he does care about these
people he loves he died for these people
just the same as you and I and if he if
you think that he is not wanting us to
help them just like anybody else that is
within our borders then we're completely
we're wrong we're off on that I mean
it's it this is this is Christianity
101. yeah yeah
I'm I'm excited to hear that message
Pastor
um let me tell you uh we we I and I
believe all of us I mean there's a gap
right now and and our people the the
people on this call that are looking for
ways to help these are people
experiencing homelessness potentially
close to where you live maybe in your
city all over the the you know at least
here in the U.S they're getting bust all
over the place you know and so
um you know maybe together we can we can
have a follow-up meeting to figure out
how we can you know figure out how to
help these people
um you know uh as well so yeah we'll see
and that's what that's what I've been
thinking like for people who who are
saying hey I would like to lead out like
something uh with something like this in
my area right right maybe we can maybe
we can do a special training for those
people so this wouldn't just hey
everybody it's we're looking for people
who are seriously like look I want to do
something in my area yeah and I need to
hear what are some of the ways I can do
it some of the things that I can do yeah
and we want you know we want living
manner to not only bless people
through the word
but we need our people
um to be actively
engaged in Hands-On Ministry and we need
that to be happening around the globe
yeah yeah we yeah we do I I believe I
believe that's what God would would want
you know he he want us to really be
stepping in the gap
for the people suffering in our
communities you know and that's what
he's called us to do I just want to say
I I there's a ton of comments I'm seeing
come in that are asking questions I'm
yeah I'm actually going to go through
all of them and I'm going to answer you
guys so don't don't think I'm you know I
won't answer you because there's a lot
of questions coming in and I I know
we're probably ending here soon so just
oh no feel free to answer as they come
feel free to answer oh really oh okay
all right well I missed a bunch
do as many as you can or what you can
catch up with um as you're kind of going
through it I'll just say you know
because I'm I'm also seeing those
questions and people are really engaged
which we want them to be they're like
I'm 100 down I want to help I want to
get involved and we want them to get
involved and so this is the reason why
we did this program today to inspire and
just to see the needy you're right this
was so timely like what's going on in
the country right now yeah
um specifically
your ministry can and hopefully the
ministry that will all like um
participate in can meet the needs of
people right now
um
you know what I did not hear from Eric
was what's your status he just fulfilled
the need of people that needed help and
and we live in a climate now that
everything has been so politicized that
we forget the humanity of people like
think about how would you feel not being
not being able to shower for a month how
would you feel knowing that you're going
You're not stable you're going from one
place to another and you're not being
treated just with human thickness you
know dignity
you can't feed your children and people
will say well they shouldn't stayed home
while they couldn't feed their children
there either
it's it's so I mean I remember there was
one guy recently
um we
we you know he came we met him that day
you know got got him some clothings food
got him a shower and um we found there's
one particular shelter that we're
calling directly their leader their
executive director and he's making
exceptions for these people to stay
temporarily while we try to get them
into housing and um and I remember that
day we got him into a shelter at the end
of the day and um
he cried you know he's like I haven't
slept in a bed in months
and you know it's just moments like that
that are like man like we need to we
need to do something you know
um I I see a question here no idea how
do they get medical insurance so
assistance medical assistance right so
um so it so we actually help we have a
partnership with an organization that
gets people IDs so last month they got
about 40 people
um IDs birth certificates and social
security cards they just use one of our
offices and uh and so that's how we you
know that's one of the first steps for a
lot of people is getting them the right
identification because their stuff gets
stolen on the street
um you know so and they lose it and
sometimes we even help store some of
that stuff to make sure that that they
don't lose it you know on the street so
yeah somebody's saying I want to start
assault in Nashville Tennessee and I
know you mentioned and we just talked
about
um
you know trying to plan something where
they can get this information I mean
we'd like for living manage to to host
some online setting where Eric can come
back Mommy can come back and we can
actually present all that information so
people who want to start this in their
areas can get the information that they
need they may not be connected to a
local church there just with us but they
have enough people that they can get a
group together that can do this and that
was candy if candy can message me
um if she's in the Nashville area she
can message me and we we can try that oh
yeah you're in that you're in Nashville
no Huntsville oh that's right you're
wearing that Madison technically I'm
sorry just come live and joined us in
the studio actually today
he's only about 30 so minutes away but
and that's good I want you to connect
with her lewami I also want us to and
we're just talking this is real time
talking about this but you know host
something
um in the very soon like within the next
couple of weeks and Eric and loamy we
need you there of course to present
um this information so we'll have some
type of sign up list speaking of that if
you want to get alerts of everything
that uh living man church is doing
um and that we can send that on the
screen or put it in the chat
um you text and that should be coming up
LM
um thank you LLC and yeah there it is
four five seven six so if you're not
getting alerts please sign up send that
text right now and then we will let you
know when we're going to do this
um this meeting so if you're interested
in starting at something like salt in
your city that Eric and luami will even
assist to helping to give you
information about that because I can I
can feel the excitement and the need
that people are are feeling and wanting
to get involved the ministry is
absolutely amazing listening to the
stories of what people are are going
through
um and what their experiences are like
is heartbreaking but it's it's
heartbreaking to hear those stories but
when you get involved in help it is the
greatest that God does allows us to be
able to help for us it helps us it
blesses us it blesses them but it
blesses us as well like you will it's
just an amazing feeling like you have a
great job Eric
it was it was always when salt started I
had always dreamed that I would be able
to do this ministry full-time we're
we're an all-volunteer organization for
eight years and uh I finally was able to
quit my job last year April 1st and I've
been doing it full time since then
I I can I can testify that this brother
really believes in what he's doing he
was finishing his Masters he was working
the job full time you know he was
engaged I mean
I I never see this brother sleep and it
was because his heart for people and and
I could testify as somebody who who
lived with him and so this is not just
for show he he really put his heart
Blood Sweat and Tears into
into the people that that he's investing
in and
amen even finishing his degree he
understood that this degree is
connecting to help people and Inspire
other people to do you know fulfill the
need in the community so
um he's he's not someone who talks a lot
but when he does is very uh
it's very important to hear and and I
appreciate that uh from Eric because he
he's not someone who talks that he lives
it and he does a lot more doing than he
does talking so I I just want to say
that was that was before I was married
now my wife taking care I get sleep you
know she when I when I'm about to
comment I'm posting tonight that's not a
good idea maybe you shouldn't post that
like okay we love you and mellies thank
you for uh
you know
um yes wives are amazing yeah
um
I saw a question I saw a question about
the water tank we hook up to a we hook
our trailer to a hose so we make sure
that um so the good thing about that is
our water tank Can Only Hold enough
water for maybe 30 showers with the hose
we can do pretty much an unlimited
amount of showers if we have a dump uh
connection hooked up
um I saw another comment about you know
people experiencing homelessness don't
go to shelters sometimes or don't like
to go to shelters
um there's there's definitely a reason
for that we surveyed and found out that
a lot of people got their stuff stolen
in shelters they don't feel safe in
shelters
um people would rather sleep in their
car than be in a shelter because of some
of those things
um so that's that's something to
definitely take you know take into
account
um it's not necessarily that they don't
want to be in a shelter I mean right now
for the past couple months of four or
five months the shelters have been
totally full I mean there's nowhere for
them to go there's there's I mean the
numbers are growing I mean the first
three months of this year we saw us
about 600 new people to to our services
you know every month
after that we've seen 200 300 new people
to our services every month it's crazy
it's it's just continuing to grow and
there isn't enough resources out there
you know what I mean so
um yeah
we want we we want people to
uh understand that
this ministry may not be up their alley
you know what I'm saying like there may
not be a need where they are right uh
for this type of ministry but
surveyed maybe not on the scale but
there's a need for every Community for
yeah but I mean I think survey the need
of your community and ask yourself what
can what can I do right how can I get a
how can I uh maybe create a team around
me that we could you know get together
and do this ministry for our community
because
that is where
you know you don't keep salt in a jar
right
I mean you keep it in a jar but the
ultimate's purpose you gotta use it you
got to use it yeah well and and I do
want to I do want to elaborate on what
you just said because working with Eric
and working with homeless you know with
the home our homeless uh friends
um when we started doing that tutoring
thing little did I know that
four years down the road that was going
to be my passion my calling as far as
providing mentors for you know mentoring
for
um inner city youth specifically and and
seeing that there's a need that over 60
46 million uh young people between the
age and eight eight and eighteen don't
even have a an adult present in their
life right and so
that was my passion but it stemmed from
working with salt seeing the needs then
that that you know as we did the
tutoring thing in that neighborhood Eric
that seed was planted a little that I
know that was going to Blossom so
what started with salt became another
passion for myself and just for
everybody what what whatever need that
you see needs to be fulfilled
do your bestly ability to fulfill it you
know yeah yeah and and I just want to
say
um so we have we when it comes to
presenting salt to other churches and
stuff we definitely have a system in
place that we've we've used for other
churches as well that have also started
we have a branch in Daytona in Tampa a
potential Branch happening in
Tallahassee and we actually have one
near San Francisco that's just getting
going
um so we want you to have a branch in
Huntsville Alabama yeah Huntsville
eventually will be there you know we
have so we have a Outreach pastors wil
Fredo and Joffrey are and myself are
really taking the lead and and uh uh we
you know we have that system that we
kind of go and teach others and and
consult others and that kind of thing so
so yeah it's uh you know
um definitely uh I guess Pastor Myers um
you said you would like try to maybe
coordinate something in the future yeah
we are definitely we want to we want to
partner with you guys our church living
Mana Church wants to partner with you
guys
um and in any way but also to help
educate our members and viewers and how
they can do something like this in their
communities or get you know just being
able to help those who are in need in
their communities and so we are going to
plan and orchestrate
um a town hall meeting I don't know if
that's the name of it but something
where they can ask their questions you
can share they can get the information
and resources and everyone who's
listening to this and you're wanting to
know when that's going to happen you
need to sign up to get our text alerts
so you'll know we're gonna we're gonna
blast it there to so you could know when
we're going to be doing this in the next
couple weeks I was just
doing some theological thinking
and something just hit me man like Jesus
did not just say you are the light of
the world and when you think of the
light of the world right you're thinking
of like
truth you know what I'm saying you're
thinking of letting your light shine and
people seeing that and seeing you know
the uh
what the truth has done for you
but he couples it with you're the salt
of the earth
so it sounds like on one hand he's
saying let your light shine you know the
truth you're understanding your
knowledge that should be people should
see what this has done for you but then
salt
is actually getting out there and
mingling and doing good for the people
[Music]
we can we can have light but no assault
which is interesting you know we're
gonna preach and we're gonna you know
this is the truth and this is the truth
this is the truth but if we're not also
solved
then we got we're missing half of the
work right amen
amen yeah pretty much though
I already see a sermon developing uh
I'm about to preach right now okay hold
up now he might find his way in there I
I want to thank everyone as I'm as as
I'm here I looked at my phone just now
and I see people are have been donating
throughout this whole thing I mean I
think we've raised almost 1300 bucks
um just from people
yeah so praise God uh thank you guys for
contributing to the work amen amen
praise God Amen yes that warms our heart
well you're this is not the last time
you're gonna see brother Eric or brother
loamy there was people who wanted to
connect with you loan me about your
youth about did you see that they wanted
to know how to contact you so yes like
Eric I'll go back to the chat and
comment okay okay yeah okay so I saw
that too so
um we're definitely this eating that
we're going to have so we can get more
information on how the rest of us in our
areas can start this type of ministry it
doesn't have to be exactly like it but
just you know get something going uh
that will be happening soon so please
sign up so you can get alerts so you
don't miss it
um but we just want to thank you for you
know just want to thank you for the
ministry like yeah it's such a blessing
those who are being served by your
ministry and for your volunteers and
everybody a part of your team it truly
truly is a blessing it's inspiring to
ever to the rest of us
um and just I just praise God on how
he's using
um your ministry to be able to help
other people it truly is a blessing we
just want to thank both of you for for
coming on and sharing someone who
doesn't talk a lot you did great yeah
Eric did you have a video that you
wanted to share uh I I mean I can I can
share a video if people want to see a
visual I don't know if do people want to
see
into the yeah I think you just you're
gonna share your screen right yeah yeah
um
let's see here
while he's doing that I just you know
again really encourage everyone to
I mean just if this didn't inspire you
to want to go out and do something like
right now today even like I I don't know
what is I mean that this ministry and
what they're doing
um is just impacting people and touching
lives in areas that
you know as a church we haven't
um
I mean we have Adra and we go into
different countries and do great things
in service for and we you know all
support Adra and what the church does
there but in our own local uh
metropolitan cities it doesn't have to
be metropolitan cities just in our own
areas
um sometimes the churches are you know
missing uh the boat yeah on that so we
want to make sure that this church
doesn't miss the boat and those who are
a part of this church as well and hoping
that other people will get involved too
but definitely share your video if can
you guys see it right now can people see
it yeah there it goes all right here he
goes
so this is a walkthrough of our services
this is our friend Richie who's
experiencing homelessness right now
um but he he uh he agreed to help us
with this video to show what it looks
like so oh
can you hear it
turn it up a little bit
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
that's powerful
I'll send the link I'll put the link in
the for people if they want to see it
um yes and they can share it as well
yeah they can share it as well
well we just want to uh you know thank
you uh both for for jumping on um true
blessings it's really a blessing yeah
where we just looked at the uh
the Practical aspect of
of you know Hands-On Ministry and uh I'm
yeah I'm about to talk about the
the spiritual aspect and how we
how
we approach issues like this really
reflect who we are on the inside who we
really are on the inside yeah and so
um yeah you know this is uh
one thing that I that can you guys hear
yeah yeah okay
um
listen you know
the profits in the Old Testament uh
Jesus when he came
uh these people were sometimes least
liked by the people that profess God
because
the prophets usually weren't
they weren't condemning the atheists the
non-believer the they were condemning
the very people who claimed to serve God
and yet were
not showing compassion not showing love
not showing
the attributes of the character of
Christ and um
and that's why they would Stone the
prophets right
um sometimes we like to hear
how how how God loves us more than
everybody uh let me stop preaching yeah
you're preaching I'm just gonna let me
just say and the people aren't going
anywhere they're gonna stay tuned yeah
stay tuned because you want to hear this
message and the
um the link to Salt was just put in the
chat you might have to go up just a
little bit and then somebody also asked
if we could re-put the the number that
they can sign up for living manage
Church to get notifications because they
don't want to miss that meeting
um so if we can put that as well
um yeah and let me say we what we hope
to do is um
we hope to be able to ultimately
uh have a dedicated Sabbath yes where
we're just you know we're telling our
members and everybody go out into your
community and do your thing right and
we're going to talk about it right so
we'll talk about that you're gonna get
more information about that yeah we want
to be known as a church that is meeting
people's needs I mean we want to we want
them to be fed by the word and they're
practical needs but we want to meet
their physical needs as well and so we
want to be known as that and that is our
goal and you guys are a part of that
because you are our church
um and you live in all the different
communities around the around the
country around the world so
um we look we look forward to engaging
um with uh this ministry and these
brothers some more and you participating
so yes this has been an amazing
um Sabbath school you know just to just
to hear what the ministry is doing and
please continue to worship with us as we
are going to move into the Divine
worship service and you'll you'll hear
more about this sounds like the summer
is going to be really a blessing uh from
God don't forget after the sermon we can
all talk about these things that we're
learning some of the ideas how you've
been inspired through alter are live and
so that's right after so make sure you
join that but with that we're going to
close uh with prayer but not just close
with prayer if you have prayer requests
um and let's remember to pray for him
forging the uh Gregory Hall okay yes and
um in that situation that we pray for at
the beginning let's keep them in prayer
and if you have any other prayer
requests put it in the chat now because
the prayer team is going to be praying
and brother Terry is going to be praying
as well over these prayer requests so
all right let's let's close in prayer
heavenly father thank you Lord for
raising this ministry up uh to be uh the
salt of the earth Lord I pray that as we
have talked today Lord that people that
are watching from all around the world
uh will be inspired by this ministry to
to uh launch out into their own
Ministries in their local areas please
use them beyond what they what they
think is even capable Lord use us beyond
what we think is capable and uh Lo we
pray that the members of living Manna
will make a difference in this world
um please Lord uh you've raised up this
church for such a time as this amen uh
please help us to fulfill this will as
our prayer in Jesus name amen amen amen
amen amen amen
[Music]
deep down in the South Pacific there's
an Eden Lake Island Paradise it's hard
to describe with words it's beauty is
breathtaking it's climate is relaxing
people are welcome it's culture is
enriching it's food is fulfilling and
its water is refreshing
[Music]
perhaps these melanesian islands are
best known in the world by the water
that punches The Thirst thousands of
people each day the natural Artesian
water of Fiji is the number one imported
bottled water in the United States and
has enjoyed in over 60 countries around
the globe and while most have never seen
this beautiful land many have been
refreshed by its soft and smooth it is
bottled right at the source high in the
unspoiled rainforests of the largest of
the Fijian islands with sea level
as tropical rain falls upon pristine
rainforests it filters through layers of
volcanic rock gradually Gathering
natural minerals and electrolytes
essential for the human body this
life-giving water collects in a natural
Artesian aquifier deep below the surface
of the Earth protected from external
elements and uncontaminated by man
Untouched by humans unto you un spirit's
cap and put it to your lips
[Music]
now it's a little pricey in the States
but here in Fiji it's very affordable
and we've been blessed by being hydrated
by it day after day you see water is
essential to every form of life every
living self plants and animals and
humans depends on water in fact three of
the five quarts of blood in the blood
vessels of our body is water and of
every 10 pounds of our weight seven of
it is water without water to drink life
is just unsustainable
water is also a natural wonder chemical
formula is H2O which means for every
part of hydrogen there are two parts of
oxygen now oxygen is flammable and
hydrogen readily burn but when uniting
hydrogen and oxygen into wall you have
the liquid that has the part to quench
blazing fires and satisfy burning thirds
water is not only essential for survival
it's also satisfying for life
and in the same way this is exactly what
God is to us you see just as this Fijian
water fell from tropical Skies to
saturate the soil of the air so to The
Healing Rain Jesus Christ
descended from Heaven to Earth to
saturate the soul of our lives and to
revive and refresh our souls he is the
heavy rain and the living wall
uncontaminated by the blush of sin full
of the minerals of grace and the
electrolytes of power ready to fill the
empty bottles of our life
so are you thirsty today
have the longings of your life remain
unfulfilled and empty have you been
drinking from the polluted Springs of
sin and selfishness
or maybe you feel yourself dying in a
drought of discouragement and despair
spiritually dehydrated by family issues
health problems paralyzing addictions
paying for rejection or plaguing
loneliness
well if so hear the words of the Living
Water to you today
Jesus said If any man thirsts let him
come to me and drink he
is in me as the scripture says out of
his heart would fall rivers of Living
Water
as good as it is this Fiji Water can
only punch me for a little while for
Jesus said whoever drinks of the water
from the whales of this world will
thirst again but whoever drinks of the
water that I shall give will never
thirst but the water that I shall give
him will become in him a fountain of art
springing up into everlasting life
foreign
let us go to the water source and as we
do Christ will not only fill up the
empty bottles of our life but he will
also export us into the world as living
containers to share the water of Hope in
a world that is dying of spiritual
Fitness so let us come so that we can
all go and that the Water of Life can
freely flow
foreign
shaking
Miranda is driving us thank you for
helping us bro you're welcome you're
welcome yesterday I was spring you can
think a little bit he answered the
phrase it was quick it was fast respond
yeah so many people have said words of
encouragement and prayers it really held
me up for sure yesterday he gave me
power last night when we preached on
baptism I preached right after this
took place and
I was weak or like fainting before I got
up to speak but when I was behind that
Pope with him it was just it was
Supernatural power there
all those people came to the front gave
their hearts to Christ
many wet eyes last night the spirit of
God moved in a powerful way the officer
just
said that they found our stuff praise
God special thanks to this guy so the
guy we thought guy who robbed us was
actually the one who's trying to help us
we do one live they look upon God as one
that's trying to rob our joy a God that
just wants to make our life miserable
with a whole bunch of restrictive
burdens but we don't realize that the
very one that we think is trying to rob
us
it's the one that's trying to save us
amen mercy upon us so we're in the
police station now we can't really film
here inside we're gonna continue the
story later on
foreign
[Music]
a whole bunch of things and I got caught
and I got arrested just like you you
know handcuffed had to sit in jail and I
felt so bad so I know how you feel man
today I get to travel all over the world
and help people and share hope to others
even though I made mistakes in the past
still has a plan and a purpose for us
same thing he did for me he can do for
you too man do you know Jesus you've
heard about him before
we got on the cross man to forgive us of
our sins God has a perfect for you he
loves you and he wants you to he wants
to use you to do great things let him
change your life and you're 17 years old
you can be anyone you can do anything
with your life you probably felt like
you had to steal so you can get money to
take care of your family or whatnot but
when you serve God he's gonna take care
of him so I want you to know that we
love you brother God loves you man all
right
can I pray with you
Father in Heaven Lord I want to pray for
my brother here Lord this is your son
and you love him you die from it and you
have a great plan and purpose for his
life and I pray Lord that he will turn
his life over to you and you would help
him to use his energy his time and his
his talents and his influences to to do
good in the world I pray that you're
helping to feel your love and to feel
your forgiveness and I pray Lord that he
and his family will be in your Eternal
Kingdom for we never have to steal never
have to grow hungry thank you Lord for
hearing this prayer in Christ's name
amen
so I'll be praying for you man I can
forget you and I hope that you won't
forget me too and uh God loves you man
uh when you leaving all right brother
but before we leave just wanted to thank
thank you and and your wonderful team uh
overnight we were able to find all our
all our possessions most of it at least
and that was very quick thank you guys
so much for taking the time going door
to door and just helping us it was a
very devastating experience yesterday
keep you folks in prayer as you continue
to keep this community safe that the
angels will protect you as you seek to
protect others I'm wondering if I can
just have a prayer for you and Father in
Heaven Lord want to thank you so much
for your great love and your mercy
towards us Lord I want to thank you so
much for the officers and the law
enforcement the team here Suva and how
they quickly responded and they did
their jobs well but we pray Lord that
you'd send angels to protect each one of
them I ask Lord in Jesus name that you'd
bless each one of them from the crown of
their head to the soul of their feet
bless this police station and everyone
that works here we pray that Angels
would be always in this place we thank
you for hearing and answering this
prayer in Jesus name we pray amen amen
God bless you yeah thank you brother
thank you great job thank you
this is the man who helped us so last
night when we preached at our seminar we
told the experience of what happened
and so happens the deputy Police
Commissioner Fiji was watching our
program and he responded and he called
all his his workers and uh told them
that we needed that they needed to solve
the case
and so praise the Lord and the Lord used
him to answer the prayers of his people
and so we just want to praise God for
that okay so we just got a text on my
phone dear Pastor
I spoke with you a while ago I hope you
are satisfied with the work of my
officers
I was unhappy when I watched your
grievance last night during the seminar
there is a cell in my house attended by
the community members I immediately
contacted my officers to immediately
follow up and I am thankful that you
have experienced the service we provide
hinaka Deputy Commissioner of police
we're very satisfied
I'm gonna go back to the river to the
waterfall the devil stopped us yesterday
but not for long
nothing can stop God's work so we're
gonna go back I'm not gonna let the
devil win let's go
don't be sorry you know when I was about
his age I was arrested before
so just about 24 hours ago right here at
this exact spot the devil stole my
camera equipment he didn't steal my joy
he didn't steal my peace tried to stop
God's work but God's word can't be
stopped and so we're here again by God's
grace even though yesterday he stole my
camera equipment
we're able to steal some Souls from his
kingdom as last night over 50 people
here in Suva responded to the baptismal
appeal and gave their hearts to Jesus so
the Lord has already won the victory the
Devils that heated defeated enemy all he
can do is
all he can do is distract us
but God has won the victory wow what an
amazing day we had today
from the tragedy of yesterday
we experienced Triumph today
yesterday was a mess today is a message
yesterday was the test today is the
testimony yesterday we were victims but
by God's grace today we were remained
victorious in Christ
with all this happened we just want to
thank God and
even though we had a difficult time
yesterday we still love Fiji
Fiji time
[Music]
thank you
let's go
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
all right if you can hear me put a one
in the chat
and I was just saying welcome welcome
living Mana church family we are so
happy that you are here with us today
okay all right there's a one so you can
hear me continue to put a one I see one
one all right all right welcome welcome
welcome
um we are just so happy that you're here
uh let us know where you're watching
from put in the chat uh we'd love to see
it if you just if you were already with
us during Sabbath School time you don't
have to re-put it but if you are new to
our church service
um please let us know where you're
watching from so we can do a special
welcome to you if this is your very
first time uh watching uh living man of
Church online with us put a two because
there's a lot of ones going up right now
but put it two if this is your very
first time worshiping with us we want to
say a special uh welcome to you I see we
have Bakersfield California we have uh
Maryland San Diego it's like we have all
right
um so welcome from the Carolinas
Colorado Denver Colorado special welcome
to all of you we are so happy got a lot
of Californians today amen amen my home
state
um Pennsylvania Maine I heard it's
beautiful in Maine haven't been there
want to get there Montana haven't been
there but I heard that's beautiful as
well welcome Florida welcome
um Texas all right Tahiti I want to go
there I've been wanting to go there so
welcome
um welcome
um the the Kevin from Tahiti thank you
for worshiping with us today New Jersey
Oregon Antioch California Special
welcome to all of you we're very happy
that you were here with us if you missed
Sabbath school today man did you miss a
treat but it's okay you can go back and
watch the replay
um it was truly an inspirational
testimony of what um the ministry salt
is doing
um in the in that community in Florida
and Orlando and actually different areas
of Florida as well and so we've been
inspired here at Living Mana church and
so we are going to definitely be
connecting with salt they are going to
do a presentation for our church and for
our members and for our guest members
um so you can get involved in learning
how you might be able to Ministry like
that in your community so if you have
not already signed up for our alerts
that you can get from our church
whenever we're doing something
I want you to do that now that's going
to be on the screen how you can do that
you can text I don't want to mess it up
so I'm going to let it come on the
screen it's about to come on the screen
now about how you can sign up for the
alerts there it is text lmoc to
84576 and then you will get these alerts
about when we're going to have that
meeting with salt also when we're going
live with our weekly programming our
mental health Mondays true Health
Tuesdays our prayer meeting our service
with um doctor our meeting with Dr
Pandit as well as you know people are
really growing and learning as they are
just learning how to prove the existence
of God without I always say without even
using the Bible but just using other
things Dr Panda is really educating us
on that and so we just praise God but we
don't want you to miss any of those
things that we are doing what we want
you to be reminded so if you sign up you
will get alerts about when all of our
meetings are happening mean and also you
don't want to miss that very special
meeting that we're going to be doing
with salt Ministry so we can learn how
we can
um start Ministries like that in our own
local communities because that's really
what this is all about I mean we get so
fed here
um on living uh in this church for
living Manna we have we have Pastor
Myers my husband who who feeds us every
Sabbath we have great guest speakers we
have during the week we are fed through
those who lead out in that and so we get
a wealth of just spiritual food and it
is a blessing to our lives practically
but we want to go out and do service for
others that God has called us to be the
salt of the earth and so we want to meet
people's needs their physical needs
whatever it is that we can do for other
people to to be the the hands and the
feet of Jesus we want to do that and we
want to equip you our members of our
viewers we want like to help you to be
able to do that in your community so
definitely sign up to get the alert so
you can know when uh the meeting is we
are just we have just been so blessed
you know I was just thinking like our
very first Sabbath was April 9th and God
has really been blessing
um this this church this ministry and
it's because of you it's because if
you're faithful you guys show up every
Sabbath you show up during the week
you've been financially giving and truly
God is just showing us like yes this is
what I've called you to do at this time
and because it is touching people's
lives in such a way he is really really
blessing and so we just praise God
because it was a leap of faith it was as
you know we stepped out into the unknown
not knowing exactly how would this work
what will this look like well people
really uh come back week after week and
we see that it's happening and so we
just praise God uh we praise God for
each and every one of you I want you to
know this you know our church is a
church we believe in prayer our prayer
team is an amazing prayer team and they
lead out every Wednesday for power
Wednesdays
um and it is such a blessing but they
are right now live waiting and looking
for your prayer requests they want to
prayer Pray over your needs
um and so please put in the chat uh what
your prayer needs are brother Terry is
going to get to many of them in a few
moments here when he leads us in prayer
but I also want to see if we can put in
the chat the email for the prayer team
and so you can email them your prayer
request and they will pray over your
prayer request you'll get an email
letting you you know that they've been
praying
over your request
um and so please put that in the chat
your prayer request it's it's there now
prayer at livingmanna.live that is the
email that you can use to email your
prayer request and trust me this prayer
team they don't just say we're going to
pray for you they pray for you so please
put that
um in the chat
um we want to let you know how you can
can continue to support the church uh we
say thank you because so many of you
have been financially supporting the
church and we just want to say thank you
but we just want to let you know how you
can continue to do that there's various
ways that you can do that one of the
ways is that you can give your offering
through cash app and that is as you see
on the screen it's dollar sign living
man at church and you can give your
offering that way you can also go to our
website which is livingmanna.church and
you can click on the offering tithe uh
button there and you will be directed to
Adventist giving Adventist giving has a
virtual type envelope you can give your
tithe there the tithe that you give
supports the northeastern conference
which is the conference that this church
living Mana church is in and that
supports the worldwide church you can
also give your offering there with which
supports living Mana church and the
things that living matter church is
doing so that helps us to be able to get
all the equipment we need to be online
to be able to continue to do Ministries
that we offer during the week and to
begin to launch new Ministries and so
you can add Venice giving and you put
living man a church in there and you can
be able to give that way you can also
mail in your tithered offering and the
address is there on the screen the P.O
box 428 Owens Crossroads Alabama
35763 and just just note on uh on the
check or envelope how much is retired
how much is for offering so we can make
sure that it goes to the right place and
we are just very thankful for your
faithfulness it is truly a blessing uh
the church so that the church can can do
the things that God is calling us to do
we have a very faithful team that we are
working with that our board members and
we are trying to do exactly what God is
calling us to do for this time so we can
get the gospel out to the world and we
know that you know all of you know so
many people are online right they're
online they're on their smartphones and
so that's where we want to show up we
want living Mana to show up right there
where they're at so we can introduce to
them uh the things that God has led us
to share you know we know so many we
know so many people are dealing with
mental health issues or health issues
um they need prayer some people just
don't even believe in the existence of
God there's other Ministries that we
want to begin to share as well as part
of living mana's uh programming and so
with all of that people are are on on
their phones online and we want to have
our advertising right there so they can
see it all they have to do is click on
it and they will they will be blessed
and God the holy spirit will do the rest
and so we just um that is that is our
goal and when you give you are
supporting uh the ministry for us to be
able to continue uh to be able to reach
people the advertising that it takes to
be able uh to do that online and so we
thank you for your faithfulness
um we thank you for your prayers we
really know that you are praying and
that you support uh this church and this
ministry that God has called us to do at
this time
and at this time I'd like to just pray
and thank all of you for uh your prayers
and for your giving and just ask God to
continue to bless this ministry so that
we can go into all the world uh with the
gospel if you please just bow your heads
with me as we pray
dear heavenly father Lord we thank you
um just so much just Lord the way you're
leading
um and then people's hearts for brother
Eric the the testimony and the ministry
that he started
um with salt Lord we all need to be
inspired to do something like that in
our communities so we just thank you for
how you lead in our lives to want to
help and to connect with people and so
Lord we just praying that you would use
this church that you would use our
members our our faith members those who
who watch
um every week but maybe a member of
another church we just pray that you
would use all of us to to do exactly
um and to do ministry in a practical way
like Saul is doing and just reach the
people in our own communities and Lord
we we know that you have called us all
to do this in a specific way and so just
show us reveal that to each individual
on how you want them to do it Lord I
Thank you for those who have been giving
financially to the church Church to
support what we are doing here we they
are so faithful and we just praise you
for putting that upon their heart as
well
Lord we ask that the Holy Spirit we
continue to be with the rest of our
service that it will be a blessing to
those who are live viewing live right
now and for those who will watch later
we just pray that the Holy Spirit would
penetrate their hearts you know the the
Holy Spirit and you know their
individual situations so let the message
and the music and the prayer speak to
them in a very special way we ask all
these things in Jesus name amen
you don't have to worry
and don't you be afraid
Joy comes in the morning
[Music]
troubles they don't last always
for there's a friend in Jesus
foreign who will wipe your tears away
and if your heart is broken
[Music]
just a little to lift your hands and say
oh I know that I can make it
I know that I can stand
no matter what may come my way
my life is in your head
praise the Lord Saints
although
that amazing worship song was
interrupted I want to say we know that
our life is in his hand
and if you can say that with me today
you know that your life is in the
Master's Hand why don't you just put a
Hallelujah right there in the chat this
morning Saints I know my life is in your
hands
you want to give you God praise today
and we want to thank him for allowing us
to serve in this living man of ministry
thank God for
drawing us and food blessing us and
keeping us through our storms and
through our trials yeah I see you in the
chat there's Saints Hallelujah
everywhere you're watching from and
listening from praise God we see all the
beautiful saints of God
and as we prepare to go to the throne of
grace we just want to start off today we
want to enter into the courts God's
courts with Thanksgiving in our hearts
went into his course with praise want to
just lift him up and Magnify Him it can
look crazy sometimes it can look
impossible sometimes it can look like
you ain't gonna come out you're gonna
look like you're about to lose your mind
gonna look like you at the end of your
wit hold on Saints don't give up don't
give in don't let go of your faith like
brother Taj said there's one more thank
God for turning our tests into a
testimony I want to thank God for taking
our message what's a mess today and
making it a message tomorrow somebody
watching right now your message and
thank God for you being here and leave
here today and go out and be a message
to somebody tomorrow
and so precious father as we come before
the throne of grace
God we give you praise we ain't here
trying to put on those show we mean it
because we've been through it and we've
done seen it we thank you oh Father for
being so good and so gracious so loving
and so kind thank you for everyone
listening in and around the globe thank
you for the trials you brought us
through that taught us how to trust in
you more thank you that when we were
without you were our provider thank you
Lord God that when uh we're in trouble
you are our refuge and strength and a
very present help thank you oh God that
you never gave up on us thinking through
a patient loving and kind and we just
give you glory Lord we thank you that
you are greater
then our lack of knowing greater than
our distortions greater than the
mountains that stand before us greater
than the obstacles in our way God
greater than the weakness that we are
aware of in our own bodies greater than
our Tendencies to stray oh God your
grace is greater than our sins
Hallelujah and we just give you praise
we magnify you we choose today to lift
you up God because you are worthy you
are worthy we think that you are alive
and on the throne we thank you that you
are listening today and that you hear
the prayers of the righteous who come
before you Lord God trusting in you and
leaning upon you in Jesus name and so
Lord today we just want to thank you
especially Lord first we just want to
give you praise for this ministry of
salt
salts out there doing it God they're
doing it and we pray that we'll be
inspired today that the church listening
will be inspired heavenly father to uh
you know as we're out there you said go
feed my sheep and we're trying to do
that Lord God in your in your strength
and power but may we mingle some salt in
that food we're laying before these
people in the world that are hurting
that are dying that are lost give us uh
love and compassion Lord in our service
that we take time to because some people
Lord what they need more than anything
else they don't really care what we know
until they know and can look Us in the
eyes and know that we truly care that
we're truly sincere that we're serving
them in the name of one who is touched
with the feelings of their infirmities
father God when some people just need
their decency their dignity back some
people just need that contact back with
Humanity again with somebody just need
to know that somebody cares and that
their life is worth something thank you
Jesus for filling our hearts with that
love and father we thank you for living
around the church I thank you for Pastor
a minor and sister retante who are
family who are friends who are pastors
to us and counselors to us Lord in
lights and examples thank you for this
amazing Ministry and this amazing vision
and what you are doing even before
today's discussion thank you for the
living manner Church board who have been
already discussing ways to get mobilized
and to get out there and do things Lord
God you've been showing us some
incredible stuff thank you for beautiful
gifts like Sister Janet Abby and some of
the awesome amazing Ministries that
she's doing it was I was just so amazed
to sit with her in her home and listen
to some of the things that she's doing
Lord and some of the amazing Miracles
and some of the changes in the way
they're impacting people's lives out
there Lord who need it the most Lord I
Thank you for these 12 practical areas
of ministry that brother Eric Camarillo
is talking about with salt Lord God lord
just give us the wisdom to know how we
can get out and meet those needs we may
be in our immediate environment right
here in our own little sphere of
influence we may not do all that salt's
doing but there's something we can do
and so open our eyes Lord that we might
see what it is you would have us to do
that has been the prayer request of many
of our beloved Saints today they put it
in the chat and we'll go through that
Lord thank you for that but many are
asking that you would speak to their
hearts and show them what you would have
them to do thank you for those prayer
requests we know you will answer Lord
help our eyes to be open or help us not
to be so busy arguing with folk who
somebody didn't look at us the right way
didn't speak to us didn't like our post
or didn't answer the right way we
arguing about some crazy little stuff
when there's really some big needs out
there that need to be met and we need to
be getting out there and doing those
things and so Jesus we thank you that
you understand and you know even us Lord
what we're in our blindness and our
ignorance and our soverness and our
sometimes uh so caught up in ourselves
and what's going on in our lives you get
it and Lord I Thank you that you're
patient with us and bringing us out of
that thinking that you put some salts
Hallelujah in our water today Lord to
get us inspired and up and moving and so
Lord I Thank you for bringing it right
into my home thank you for my lovely
wife amra and some of the things that
she's getting us involved in right here
in our own Community do thank you for
that Lord in Jesus name Lord and I thank
you for brother loamy Richardson Lord
and revelation of Hope and brother Taj
and the wonderful things that they're
doing thank you for the mentorship it is
so important that uh young uh men and
and women in the inner city need to have
a strong uh Godly mentorship Lord God
and godly examples and we just pray that
you'll continue to Blow The Wind of your
spirit into their cells as they are
opening why to see what how you would
lead them and how you would direct them
God I also want to pray Lord God for
what does Jesus looked like Ministries
up there in Spokane Washington uh
brother Sean and Crystal Cox Lord God I
know that they are doing all they can do
right there in their little Spirits
experience of influence thank you for
their hearts Lord having Hearts to help
those who are out there brother Sean's
getting out there in those streets and
Lord God he's got a he's a ball of fire
we pray you protect him and Camp your
angels about him give them to give him
the wisdom to know how to connect with
these folk and what to say and what to
do Lord supply for his resources in
Jesus name because I know he needs help
there Lord and we thank you that you are
the great provider
Lord I want to pray for Sister Janice
Morrison's mother uh uh her whose roof
collapsed and and Holmes become
inhabitable and so Lord she doesn't she
have she's got to have a place to stay
we pray you take care of her and comfort
her it can be quite a shock and Lord in
any of the emotional and psychological
uh uh things that are going on with her
Lord God but until she can get this her
home repaired and restored take care of
and watch over the Lord sister Carolina
collado's father has been struggling for
several weeks with getting his cancer
treatment Lord Jesus just step right on
in and he'll touch save and deliver do
something awesome and amazing but you
are the great provider Lord God it is
really you we're waiting on and so we
pray for Gwendolyn Vines also Father uh
uh uh she's praying that she would be
able to launch out and and I know that's
the voice of many today they want to we
want to launch out father we want to
spread our wings and open our borders
and and just move out there and to do
the things that you would do many are
attending and many are afraid you told
Timothy that you're not giving us a
spirit of fear but a power and of love
and a sound mind and some people just
don't know yet Lord but let them dip
their toe in the water and experience
Jesus working in and through them and
become addicted to the ministry
Hallelujah to seeing Jesus do uh both
will to Will and to do in and through
their lives and I just pray that that
will be uh the testimony of many today
God and God we're praying for
uh Jane Smith Lord she wants a fresh
baptism of the Holy Ghost God I need
that myself and I know many listening
today need it Lord uh we have a sister
who's been saying that she feels cold
and feel that you're distant from a
sister Natalie Kelly is praying Lord God
that you would speak to her show her in
this drought season of her life Lord
you're actually letting her to get her
Roots down deep Lord God so when the
winds and the rains and the storms come
she won't be blown away and she'll know
her God be strong and do exports Lord
we're praying for Nessa B it's asking
for a change heart she's at the labor
Lord she wants to be able to show love
and forgiveness to others you already
promised to do it God in Jesus name and
I just pray that over these coming days
and weeks you'll be able to lie get in
alignment with you through your word and
through prayer we thank you for brother
Gregory Hall Lord we're continuing to
pray for his fiancee that it will be
totally recovery and we're praying for
Down's view uh church that they would
review his transfer and he would get
transferred over to living man of
ministry he has an awesome health
message and some awesome insights he's
been a blessing to the men and we thank
you so much for his presence and our
character building class and some of the
amazing contributions you've used him to
bring to us and we just pray
strengthening build him up be a wall
about him O Lord a flaming wall of fire
around his beautiful brother in Jesus
name God and um Lord we're continuing to
pray for SDA uh rail 24 uh her kids are
in an SDA school and she wants to be
able to keep them there and needs
financial assistance watch over her and
provide for her Jehovah Jireh we thank
you in Jesus name and Alicia she's
praying for uh Alice and uh uh Germany
Lord God that they would uh uh come back
to you Lord God and Marcellus Bishop who
is experiencing some mental health Lord
that he would be able to get the
treatment and the help that he needs uh
brother Vance is is is praying Lord God
that that uh uh his friend's heart would
come back to you Lord God and so we're
just praying you uh reach out and call
them today in Jesus name and Couture
Fleming she's praying for Malik Lord God
that he would also admire that their
hearts would also be drawn back to you
in Jesus name and Lord our young brother
Enoch
who's in nursing school now who's a such
a blessing to us and we're watching you
mold and shape and change this young man
so so precious Lord God to see such a
young soul and a young heart with Zeal
for you and hunger for you and thirst
for you and he's so thoughtful and
reflective God we just pray that you
lost bring him up out of his comfort
zone he he sensed that you're giving him
that little nudge and so let him stir up
the gift that is in him Lord God as so
many other young men of our young men
need Lord God don't let them be caught
up into these Trends and these fads and
these movements that are going on in
society today that the God of this world
are using to lure our young men away
thank you for young men like Enoch Lord
uh we're also praying with our sister
Michelle Watson Grant who's praying for
our special couple and a family Lord God
that they would be able to overcome they
would be able to come closer to you that
their marriage would be blessed Lord God
and we know you're hearing these prayers
many of our marriages sister Gigi really
emphasized to us in many of our
marriages are under attack right now
outlord and so we are praying oh God
that you will help us here at Living
manner Ministries our prayer team Lord
God our women's and men's
um who are doing the character training
under the pastor's seven week program
that we would be able to come alongside
and support them and serve them Lord put
words in our mouth give us uh words from
the testimonies and and give us words
from scripture Lord and give us light
and ways to be able to open up the
sanctuary message and show them that the
answer is in the Everlasting gospel
there's never been a problem that hell
has ever came up with that heaven hasn't
already cooked up an answer to and so we
thank you God that their solution your
way oh God is indeed in the sanctuary
and so as we're going through this
program help us oh Lord God to speak
words of comfort and words of wisdom and
guidance and support may they hear your
voice and not even ours Lord to help
these uh beautiful people come through
these marriages and experience the power
of the god of reconciliation
and Lord we're also praying for hani's
mother's health she needs deliverance
from
um and and and from anger and Lord I
just pray that you watch over her touch
her body and this and anger can
sometimes be uh directly connected to
the health issue Lord I know that
personally you delivered me from
debilitating anger and rage and hatred
and I saw you just take the Stony heart
out and put in a heart of Flesh and give
me a heart of love and found myself uh
back in the days Lord God when when my
heart became callous and cold I found
myself crying over the smallest uh uh a
diaper commercial so I know you can
tenderize the heart you can make the
heart soft and tender and sensitive you
can do it God and so we just pray set
her free father from these chains
and Lord God again we want to pray with
brother Ian Nichols who who is dealing
with uh liver cancer Lord God we pray be
a Healer step in Lord God and be a
physician to this lovely one Lord we
want to also remember to thank you for
sister Patty she's always in the chat
and always being encouraging always
laboring always doing the work of the
lord always coming alongside and so we
do thank you for that and brother
Lawrence Nagy is asking for prayer for
Evelyn Nicole and Salome who have health
issues Lord God and Gwendolyn who's out
of touch with her family we pray God
that you would um just step into these
situations as we lift these beautiful
ones up before you sister Tina Wright
and her family are going through stress
and change right now and need your
presence in a special way Lord JK petite
has a friend KB who is resisting Jesus
Lord your word says is the goodness of
God that leads us to repentance and so
as we begin to close this time of
intercessory prayer father we lift you
up knowing that you are the good God no
matter how dark it is your word says the
light shineeth and darkness and the
Darkness overcometh it not those who
have prayer requests that we may have
overlooked today or didn't miss and
maybe thinking well nobody's thinking
about me and I got missed today and
maybe my problem's too big for God lord
there is nothing too hard for you and we
just pray for your revelatory power to
just burst upon their hearts and their
minds God you who commanded the light to
shine out of Darkness shine now in the
heart of your people to give the light
of the knowledge of the glory of God in
the face of Jesus Christ and we O Lord
will give you all of the glory all of
the honor and all of the praise all
God's Saints declared amen
amen
amen amen
um just wanted to
um give another
um thank you brother Terry for that
prayer and the prayers
um as we continue to to lift up all
those requests the prayer team will be
praying over your prayer request and I
want you to also pray about uh something
else to put it put a one in the chat if
you have been blessed by the reflections
of hope that evangelist apocalypse
shares with us each and every week I
know that I'm personally blessed by them
I know many of you are as well uh but
you could put a one in the chat uh so
this request is for that Ministry
um he I just spoke with him just saw him
and spoke with him this past weekend you
know and he had shared that
um he has 15 uh maybe 20 of these uh
reflections of hope you know this um
just sitting on a shelf that they need
to be the the footage has been filmed
but he is in need of an edit enter an
editor that can can put these as you
guys see it's very well done he is a
perfectionist and so he makes sure that
uh his his presentation that he presents
to us and to the world is very well done
and so he is in need of an editor uh to
be able to uh finish these 15 that he
has 15 to 20 that he has right now
um and he will be producing more and so
if uh you um if God puts it on your
heart uh that you would like to be able
to assist uh evangelist Taj in this
ministry by editing the footage that he
already has
um you can reach out to him and his
email is is on the screen it's
tajapocalyp gmail.com and you can send
him a message and say hey I'm interested
in helping you edit these projects
um and you guys can can work everything
else out uh together so if if if you are
talented in that area if God has given
you a gift in that area and you have a
heart for Ministry and want to see uh
those reflections of hopes
um messages go out into the world then
definitely contact uh brother Taj and
again his his contact information is on
the screen and so with that we're going
to continue to worship uh God today
together
um just God bless you and happy Sabbath
you don't have to worry
and don't you be afraid
[Music]
Joy comes in the morning
troubles they don't last always
[Music]
for there's a friend in Jesus
away
[Music]
if your heart is broken
just
sure foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
so in your chest and trials
down
[Music]
down and all your friends
are nowhere to be found
remember there's a friend in Jesus
who will wipe your tears away foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
Jesus I can't take it
[Music]
stand
no matter what may come my way my
mother had
your hand to say I know I can't make it
I know
I can't stand no
one may come my way
my life is in your
eyes
with
my Lord
[Music]
may come my way
my life is in
your hands my life is in your hands
my life is in your heads
my life is in your hands
my life is in your
in your hands
Life is In His Hands your life is in
his hands you don't have to worry your
life is in his hands your life is in
it no reason to be
the big heads
behind
his eyes hands up so
step back up her Square your shoulders
dry your
eyes cause you're gonna
you're gonna
make it
[Laughter]
life is in your hands my life is
[Applause]
this video
[Music]
[Applause]
my joy
[Music]
and perfect
Jesus
[Music]
compass for my pain
you're the fire and light when the
nights are alone
[Music]
and is there to hold
you're the center of my
mind
[Music]
Jesus
you are why are my pleasure
in not simple things
[Music]
foreign
Lord Jesus Jesus
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
oh my god oh
Lord
[Music]
[Applause]
Hallelujah
let us pray let us pray let us pray
Heavenly Father
we thank you Lord for
giving us this opportunity to come and
to worship before you
and Lord we pray that um you would
please speak
to your people
I prayed in Jesus name
amen
and amen
happy Sabbath everyone
um
we are going to be dealing with the
subject today
of the woke deception the woke deception
put that word in the chat for me woke
w-o-k-e
woke the woke
deception
so you're asking what is this woke
we're gonna go to the scriptures
I'm going to see some really amazing
things from several Parables we're going
to be staying in one chapter
and so we're going to be looking at
three different parables
and I believe the Lord has a word
for his Messengers for his uh people
today
um
so let's begin let's begin
uh by going to the screen and
we're going to go to the Book of Matthew
chapter 25.
Matthew chapter 25
uh we're going to start reading from
verse 1. Matthew 25
beginning with verse 1. the Bible says
here
then shall the Kingdom of Heaven be
likened unto ten virgins
which took their lamps
and went forth to meet the bridegroom
and five of them were wise
and five were foolish
they that were foolish took their lamps
and took no oil with them
but the wise took oil in their vessels
with their lamps
so the Bible here is describing in this
Parable Jesus is describing these ten
women
um five of whom are foolish
five of whom are wise
and the difference between
the wise and the foolish is what what do
we see so far according to the text what
was the one difference between the wise
virgins and the foolish virgins
the wise virgins and the foolish virgins
um the wise virgins
took oil
and the foolish virgins did not so we
see that there is a significant
difference between the wise and the
fullest we might say it like this the
wise had foresight
put that word in the chat for me please
the wise had foresight whereas the
foolish did not
uh the wise saw ahead
the wise had their eyes open
they saw ahead they had their eyes open
and uh I just got a quick question for
you
when your eyes are open what does that
mean
typically your eyes being open means
that you are what
think as opposed to your eyes being
closed
when someone's eyes are closed they are
typically in what state
yes yes yes yes good when your eyes are
open you're you're awake
when our eyes are not open
you're not awake that's the typical
yeah John Coleman says you're woke when
your eyes are open
uh if your eyes are closed
you're not awake you're not not now let
me let you know something because I know
that this word woke elicits a lot of
emotion depending on who you are
but please don't let that get in your
way right now I just want you to uh to
think about what the word just simply
means means to be awake means to be
awake that's all
um notice this notice notice on the
screen uh Ecclesiastes chapter 2 verse
14. the wise man's eyes are in his head
but the fool walks in darkness the fool
walks in darkness so so again the text
is simply showing the difference between
the Y's and the foolish the wise man
right he sees
he's walking in light the foolish walk
in the darkness and I'm going to show
you a little bit later that walking in
darkness is equivalent to being asleep
walking in darkness is equivalent to
being asleep
so
um let's go back to the screen let's go
back to the screen and and by the way
let me ask you a question real quick
what is the oil represent
I want to just see if you can you can
tell what do you think the oil
represents in this parable
what does the oil represent in the Bible
very good the oil represents the spirit
of God the oil represents the spirit of
God and I want to read something to you
very specific about the spirit of God
because it's going to help you to
understand uh something as we go deeper
into the message so so notice notice on
the screen uh in Revelation chapter 5
and verse 6 the Bible says and I beheld
in low in the midst of the throne and of
the four beasts and in the midst of the
elders stood a lamb as it had been slain
that's a reference to Jesus
um having seven horns and seven Watts
eyes
which are the seven spirits of God sent
forth into the Earth so so let's just
pause for a moment and let's put this
together
um the oil
represents the Holy Spirit but according
to Revelation Chapter 5 Verse 6 the
manifestation of the holy spirit is
actually like it's seven spirits and
then the text says that these Spirits
are the eyes
if I can put it this way and put it one
in the chat if you get this the spirit
of God is designed to keep you mentally
awake to keep your eyes open the spirit
of God allows your eyes to be open put a
one in the chat if that makes sense when
the spirit of God is in you you see what
you normally wouldn't and the spirit of
God is in you your eyes are open your
understanding has expanded
um we can say that you are awake
yes can we say that you are awake or if
we were to say it in today's terms you
are woke now please don't let that word
and and oh the word means there's a
don't don't think about that right now
I'm just talking about what the word
literally means don't put the cultural
you know so it just we're simply saying
that the spirit helps us to be awake it
helps us to walk with our eyes open it
helps us to discern it helps us to see
clearly how be when he the spirit of
Truth has come he will guide you into
all truth he's not speaking of himself
uh but he shall show you things to come
so we can agree that having the oil
means that your eyes are open which
means that you are spiritually woke can
we use that term you are spiritually
awake
all right let's keep moving let's keep
moving I want you to notice again first
Thessalonians chapter five
first Thessalonians chapter five
beginning with verse five the Bible says
here you are all the children of light
and the children of the day we are not
of the night nor of Darkness
therefore let us not what
sleep as do others but let us watch and
be sober
for they that sleep
in the night
and they that be drunken are Drunken In
The Nights
watch this guys they that sleep
in the night and they that are drunken
are drunk in the night
foreign
just told you earlier that being asleep
is or being in the dark is a synonymous
to walking in sleep or to being in sleep
to being asleep
to not
let me I'm going to use today's
vernacular not being woke so the
opposite of woke is to not be woke
it's to not be woke
so the wise
have discernment they can see
Their Eyes Are Open they are they are
woke they are awake while the foolish
walk in darkness they don't have any oil
their light as we'll see in the parable
goes out they're walking in darkness
they are asleep maybe just think to
their danger a state to their character
asleep to the truth about who they
really are they're asleep
they are not spiritually
awake
you're either woke or asleep you're
either woke or anti-woke
that's kind of a term that's used today
as well anti-wall
so so
I've got two choices before me
and I'm just speaking spiritually now
I'm not using the world's definition of
I'm simply saying I can either be
spiritually woke or spiritually
anti-woke
which means I'm spiritually awake or I'm
spiritually sleeping
uh I want you to notice
from the book Sons and Daughters of God
page 164.
those who are controlled by the spirit
of God so pause for a second
the spirit of God those who are
controlled by the spirit of God that's
the oil is that right
is that the oil that's the Holy Spirit
watch those who are controlled by the
spirit of God are to keep their
perceptive faculties what put that word
in the chat for me I just want to make
sure we're following those who are
controlled by the spirit of God that's
the oil are to keep their perceptive
faculties
awake
yeah for the time
has come when their integrity and
loyalty to God and to one another will
be tested do not commit the least
Injustice in order to gain Advantage for
yourself do unto others in small matters
as well as in great as you would what
what others would do unto you God says
you are my Witnesses you are to act in
my place so then to be woke spiritually
woke is is to have your your your
perceptive faculties to be aware that
you are standing in this world as a
representative of God
if we're to say what is the biblical
definition of walk not the worldly the
biblical definition of woke the biblical
definition of woke is to be aware that
you are standing for Jesus how many of
you would like to be the biblical
definition of woke just put a one in the
chat
that's you I would like to be
aware
that the things that I do are a
reflection of the character of God
now I wanna I wanna give to you the the
the
current cultural definition of the word
woke and it's really very interesting
but I want you to check it out
um here is the the current cultural
definition of the word woke it means to
be alert to racial
or social discrimination and Injustice
to be alert to racial or social
discrimination and Injustice
and so the question is
um does this definition of woke
fit the biblical definition of woke
does God want us to be alert
to injustices and uh whether they are
social or whether they are even
economical or or or racial does God want
us to be
sensitive
does God want us to be
sensitive to these things what do you
think
does does God in the book of James
warn about
economic Injustice robbing the the
Laborer of their hire
does God do that in the book yeah he
does so that signifies to me that God
wants us to be mentally aware to be
spiritually aware of what he views as
wrong for example economic Injustice
whatever that might mean
okay what about what about
here how about this let's just go to the
text
let's see what Micah chapter 6 verse 8
says Micah chapter 6 verse 8 tells us
this
it says he has showed thee o man what is
good and what does the Lord require of
Thee but to do justly
and to love mercy and to walk humbly
with thy God may I suggest to you that
this is the biblical definition of being
woke
it is to to do justly meaning to care
about Injustice meaning to care about
when when when when people are being
oppressed meaning to care about common
human decency and dignity
that's what the Bible says
true religion is
right so so in that context
I want to be I want to be woke and you
should want to be woke but here's the
problem the woke deception here's the
problem you see this term woke uh has
grown to become synonymous with like a
political statement
and so for a lot of Christians
they look at the term woke as having an
agenda so therefore their response is I
am not going to be woke and so there's
this whole
anti-woke right we're just using the
cultural terms now
anti-roke uh uh reaction how we're not
gonna care
we're not going to be sensitive we're
going to just deny that there is
anything wrong with what's going on
society we're going to deny that there
is uh Injustice or there is
discrimination or no no those things
don't exist this is this is America
as if Satan has led up on racism he's
like ah you know what racism doesn't
work with this people and with these
people anymore so we got to try
something new as this as if he's not up
with prejudice as if he's let up with
with Injustice of all kinds no no
beloved sin has been here from the
beginning of time and it continues to be
here today if anything has gotten
stronger it may be masked in different
ways but it's gotten stronger so watch
this
for a lot of people when they hear the
term woke and I'm gonna I'm gonna be a
little bit raw here okay when they hear
the term woke especially my white
brothers and sisters what they hear is
that oh all white people are evil all
white people are prejudiced all white
people are this and that well
I got some
some good news and bad news
here's the good news
and I got to say this carefully because
this could be a sound clip
not only I got to make sure that this
doesn't get cut off into a partial
sentence he was like look what Pastor
Mike said not only
are all white people
not good
all black people all Chinese people all
Russian people all whatever nationality
you want to choose the Bible says all
have sinned and fallen short of the
glory of God put a one in the chat if
you thought that was a good save just
now all right one in the chat if you
thought that was a good save just not I
thought that was a good seed and it is a
good seed because all has sin
and fallen short of the glory of God
that's number one that's number one
number two is this no no all white
people are not prejudiced praise God for
that
praise God that all white people are not
prejudice
praise God that there are people who
have given their lives to Christ and who
know the difference between right and
wrong praise God for that and listen
I I know of religions
black religions
who believe that white people were made
by an evil scientist named Jacob
and therefore all white people are the
are of the devil were created by the
devil beloved that is the height of
wickedness that's wicked teaching
because white people were not created by
the devil
there are some other groups that believe
that white people will be enslaved
during the millennium
because of their so-called wickedness
beloved again another teaching from the
pits of Satan no God does not hate races
God made all the races God made all
people so yeah if when I hear my black
brothers and sisters talking about the
white people are you know are evil and
they're inherently this that and that
I'm like nope
nope you're wrong that's of the devil
so I need you to understand beloved
sometimes we allow what other people
insert into a word the meaning they put
into a word we allow that to throw us
off because what's happening now is many
Christians are walking around saying I
am not woke like that's something to be
proud about
foreign
like you you let other people Define
what it means and then you reject the
thing altogether as someone said
yesterday you throw out the baby with
the bath water
why would a Christian walk around and
saying I'm not saying I'm not awake I'm
not woke
really
seriously
because the five foolish virgins beloved
listen to me
here here let me show you this let me
show you this
let's go to Matthew 22 verse 21 and see
this is where a lot of Christians really
get met mixed up
Matthew 22 verse 21.
listen to this
the Bible says here Jesus speaking or
these people are coming to Jesus
they say unto him so remember the whole
story about
so we pay taxes to Caesar or not and
Jesus says bring me a coin and they
bring the coin and then Jesus says whose
symbol whose name and figure on this and
they say unto him Caesar then Jesus said
unto them render therefore unto seeds
are the things that are Caesar's and
unto God the things that are Gods so
here's a question guys
if God calls us to render to Caesar what
is Caesar's
and unto God what is Gods remember
Caesar represents the government let's
say this way Caesar represents politics
God
is talking about our character
now let me ask you which has the higher
calling on our life Caesar or God
politics
or What God Says
absolutely the answer is God God has the
preeminence in our lives if you're a
Christian that is if you're not a
Christian I get it it's going to be
politics it's going to be Caesar I get
that but I'm talking now for the
Christian
for the Christian it's God
so here's what happens
when we allow Caesar politics to dictate
oh yeah so you know these woke people
want to talk about Justice well I'm not
gonna talk about Justice you're allowing
your Prejudice in political matters to
affect your duty to God
do I need to say that again
you are putting Caesar above God
everything for you now is divided into
two camps is it Republican or Democrat
if it's if it's Democrat it is this if
it's Republican it is that and now your
lens
is Caesar and not God
and so now Christians are at the place
watch this now Christians are in a place
right now where they are actually
celebrating and high-fiving the ill
treatment of people who have nothing to
do with politics
why because it serves The Narrative of
Caesar
of their political preference
so because woke to the average Christian
in America represents something that is
outside the will of God and oh you're
you know it's just political you don't
really care about people now people are
going around bragging I'm anti-woking
and they're talking about the the world
this and the world that all as if it's
something negative and what they're
doing is and Satan is rejoicing Satan is
laughing he's like yeah that's right you
don't be woke you're not gonna care
about that stuff and and now listen then
this is mind-blowing stuff
this is mind-blowing stuff because
because I now
am seeing Christian people rejoice
celebrate
where I never thought I would have seen
a Christian celebrate
and you know what that's doing
you got to understand what's Happening
Here Satan
is using this as propaganda against
Christianity
that's his whole goal and he's using
Christians to do it
yes Eugene we have no King but Caesar
because when you put Caesar above God
you are making Caesar King and God
subservient so now everything you do
when you even now when you come to the
Bible you're looking at the Bible
through political lens
watch this Matthew 25 verse 5 while the
bridegroom tarried they all slumbered
and slept oh Pastor there goes your
analogy they all slumbered and slept
well listen in the parable in the
parable they're waiting for the
bridegroom
watch this guys in the parable it's not
the sleeping the physical sleeping that
is negative they're all to be to be
sleeping means they just waited they
were just waiting they slumbered and
slept they're waiting for the bridegroom
nothing wrong with sleeping what was
wrong listen to me what was wrong
was that the five foolish did not have
oil the five foolish listen to me the
five foolish and the five wise slept
different kinds of sleep the five wise
slept woke
do I need to say that again
do I need to say that again the five
wise
slept aware they brought oil they had
foresight they slept aware the five
foolish slept a foolish sleep
for those of you who want to test me on
this just just go to that thing you know
that we call the spirit of Prophecy and
look at what she says was the difference
between the wise sleep and the foolish
sleep we might say
I like that Jody the foolish were
sleepwalking
the foolish were asleep before they went
to sleep
the wise were awake even though they
were sleeping
did you all catch that
the foolish were asleep before they
physically slept the wise were awake as
they physically slept
so so watch this watch what the text
says and at midnight there was a cry
behold the bridegroom cometh go ye out
to meet him then all those versions of
rose and trimmed their lamps and the
foolish said unto the wise give us of
your oil for our lamps are gone out
notice the lamps of the foolish go out
but the wise answered saying not so lest
there be not enough for us in you but go
here rather than them that's sell and
buy for yourselves and while they went
to buy the bridegroom came and they that
were ready they that were ready uh shut
themselves up they already went in with
him to the marriage and the door was
shut afterwards the other virgins say
came also saying Lord open to us but the
answer then said verily I say unto you I
know you not now why is it so
significant here's why Proverbs 6 9 says
this how long will thou sleep o sluggard
when will thou arise out of thy sleep
yet a little sleep yet a little Slumber
a little falling of the hands to sleep
so shall thy poverty come as one that
travaileth and I want as an armed man so
let's listen y'all to be anti-woke
means you're going to end up in poverty
you're going to wake up without oil
and you're going to realize that only
when it's too late
because you decided I am going to be
anti-woke
I'm going to deny that what you call
Injustice I'm gonna deny that I don't
care what it is my role in my political
role is to deny that reality
now beloved I get it in the world's
definition of woke there's a lot of
things that go against the will of God I
get that
I get that
but you need to hear me out beloved
as Christians we need to demonstrate
what true wokeness is what Biblical
wokeness is and beloved that does not
mean denying everything that the worlds
that the world happens because beloved
sometimes the Bible says the children of
Darkness are sometimes wiser than the
children of light
we cannot deny Injustice just because we
don't like the people who are talking
about it
that's stupidity
that's foolishness
so what is biblical wokism can we ask
that question what is biblical wokism
let me tell you according to the Bible
First Corinthians 15 34 says awake to
righteousness and sin not for some have
not the knowledge of God but true
wokeness biblical wokeness is awaking to
righteousness well what is righteousness
pastor
well let's check out what Isaiah 58
verse 6 says it's not this the fast that
I've chosen to lose the bands of
wickedness to undo the heavy burdens and
to let the old press go free and that
you break every yoke is it not to deal
thy bread to the hungry and that thou
bring the poor their cast out to thy
house when thou season naked thou cover
him that thou hide not thyself from
thine own flesh watch this then shall
thy light Break Forth as the morning and
thine Health shall spring forth speedily
and thy righteousness shall go before
thee that's Isaiah 58 yes y'all need to
read it again the biblical definition of
wokeness the the biblical meaning of
being awake of of of being awake to
righteousness or to be a waiter awakened
to righteousness I should say is
foreign
how we care
for others
how we care for the oppressed how we
care for the Immigrant how we care for
the stranger how we care for those who
don't agree with us politically how we
care for our brothers that's the true
test of righteousness
notice the words on the screen wake up
Brethren and sisters
do not be afraid of good works let us
not be wary and well doing for in due
season which we shall reap if we faint
not do not wait to be told your duty
open your eyes and see who are around
you and make yourselves acquainted with
the helpless Afflicted the needy may I
add in here the immigrants
hide not yourself from them from them
and seek not to shut out their needs who
gives the proofs mentioning James of
possessing pure religion untainted with
with selfishness or corruption who are
anxious to do all in their power to Aid
in the great Plan of Salvation it is so
simple and yet so so hard for so many to
grasp because so many are asleep
so many are asleep what does it mean to
be biblically woke it means to do
justice and judgment which is more
acceptable to the Lord than sacrifice
that's what it means to be biblically
woke Jesus put it this way in Matthew 22
Jesus said unto them Thou shalt love the
Lord thy God with all thy heart with all
thy soul with all thy mind this is the
first and great commandment and the
second is like unto it Thou shalt love
thy neighbor as thyself so what is the
problem with the five foolish virgins
the problem with the five foolish
virgins is that they were poor in oil
put a one in the chat if you understand
what I just said the five foolish
virgins were poor in oil they slept not
just when they were sleeping but before
they were sleeping
are you catching me
before they were sleeping they were they
were sleepwalking
and what happens is they run out of oil
now Pastor what do you mean they they
ran out of oil well what is the oil we
just saw the oil as the Holy Spirit Well
what does the spirit produce let me show
you what the spirit produces
the fruit of the spirit is what
love
not partial love love
Joy
peace
long-suffering gentleness goodness Faith
meekness temperance
that's the fruit of the spirit that's
the fruit of the oil but beloved
the anti-woke lock this oil
to be anti-woke to be sleeping means you
don't have the soil and if you don't
have this all you don't know how to love
except others agree with you you don't
know how to be patient with others but
no they gotta see you get
foreign
you think it's okay to hate in the name
of Jesus
and what happens when you don't have oil
is your fire goes out and what is fire
in the Bible according to Song of
Solomon set me as a seal upon thine
heart as a seal upon thine arm for love
is as strong as death jealousy cruel is
a grave the cause thereof of what of
Love Are coals of fire which has a most
behaving flame many Waters cannot quench
love neither can the floods drown it I
need you to understand beloved that fire
in the Bible is symbolic of love when
the oil of the five foolish virgins go
out because they are anti-woke they do
not care about others they do not care
about the injustices they don't they do
not care about about their human fellow
When It Go when they lose the oil they
are in fact losing love and what does
the bible tell us in Matthew 24 12 it
tells us that because iniquity shall
abound the what
the love of many Saw wax cold
okay
may I be real with you right now I've
been real with you and I'm gonna get I'm
about to get more of you
I am watching Christians
Christians
Christians who profess the third Angel's
messages
mocking
y'all remember the event that happened
with these with these immigrants
not really knowing what's going on and
we just had salt on and
um Eric was talking about the the
condition of these people coming in from
Venezuela and I am seeing Adventists
mocking
making jokes
give me a break
this is all political on your end and
this and that
Pastor you are of the devil for talking
about this
the outcast what I just said pastor the
devil is using you
because you're addressing how Christians
should treat other people
Pastor you're political
Pastor you are a liar
Christians
foreign
who because of political affiliation
don't want to hear about Mercy don't
want to hear about how Christians should
respond when the when when others are in
crisis they don't want to hear that why
because Caesar has trumped God
their allegiance is more to Caesar than
it is to God thus they are asleep the
oil is lacking there is no love
wait wait who are you you're not one of
us well hey bro
yeah it is what it is
hmm
and here's the thing beloved like if you
if you like to sleep you hate noise
you hate noise and a lot of people like
Pastor you need to shut up you need to
stop talking some people said to me
Pastor you need to focus on the Three
Angels messages what
listen
check out the text y'all
his Watchmen are blind they are all
ignorant they are all dumb dogs they
cannot bark sleeping lying down loving
to Slumber see when you like to Slumber
you don't want dogs around you barking
do you
did you hear what I just said when you
like sleeping you don't want dogs
barking because dogs wake you up barking
dogs wake you up out of your sleep
dumb dogs will see it a thief coming and
listen when the dog is barking all the
dog is doing is trying to protect those
that He Loves
why are you barking shut up dog
hey you know what hey
one thing I can promise you
this dog
is not shutting up
because this dog
loves his people
that is all those people like you know
you know Devil's trying to pull one over
on us he's trying to come into the house
and you guys we need to we need to we
need to be we need to not be deceived
into saying we are not going to care
about people
like come on guys like that is such an
elementary trick and yet it's working
with marvelous success
okay
stay focused on the Three Angels message
what do you know what the Three Angels
message is the Bible says the fear of
the Lord is the beginning of wisdom
you know that message that says fear God
and give glory to him
for the hour of his judgment has come
that message the fear of the Lord is the
beginning of wisdom those who fear the
lord are wise those who fear the lord
have oil which means those who fear the
lord have love mercy and it's
demonstrated in how they treat other
people how can you be talking about
preaching the Three Angels messages when
you don't love other people I don't love
you I hate you because you're homosexual
I hate you because you're a transgender
I hate you because you're an atheist I
it's us against the atheist come on
we're going to be in these cultural Wars
God never called us to be in a culture
War
God called us to be in a war to win our
enemies and you don't win your enemies
by fighting against them
God never called us to be in a culture
War
he called us to be in a war to spread
the gospel in love
to pray for our enemies to pray that
don't believe in the truth to pray for
those who are atheists and befriend them
and befriend the homosexual and befriend
the transgate gender and befriend
whoever else we need to be befriend the
political person that doesn't see things
the way that you see
and speak the truth in love
not in Anger not bitterness I hate you
hate you we get these little Christian
Gatherings and we talk about the culture
War and what they're doing and but we're
going to stand strong like we have
decided they are our enemies and there's
not much that can be done for them so we
gotta hold the flag we gotta hold the
ground but another God never called us
to a battle like that the battle he
called us he said behold I send you as
serpents uh as
yeah
I send you as Lambs Among Wolves be wise
as serpents
how are you listen listen the Bible says
in Daniel 12 3 they that be wise
five wise virgins shout sign is the
brightness of the firmament and they
that turn many of the righteousness as
the Stars forever let me ask you a
question how are you going to turn many
to righteousness by fighting against
them how are you going to turn many of
the righteousness by condemning those
who don't know God and by and by calling
other people names and and and and
thinking that it's okay and listen
listen this idea
this idea that it's okay for Christians
to laugh and to Mock and to
I'ma tell y'all straight up
that's just been introduced in the last
six years
yeah look at my face I just said it
it has become
normalized
popularized to just be like hi and and
now I'm seeing this attitude listen
y'all friends that I have in this church
who are talking to me all kinds of crazy
ways I'm like yo
what
let me tell you something back no to
this day someone and I were joking about
this uh a couple like yesterday remember
how David was like I'm not touching Saul
he is the Lord's anointed and I'm not
touching them even though Saul was as
wicked as whatever David feared God
enough to be like Saul's anointed I'm
not touching him man these days
y'all remember back in the days when if
you had the title Pastor it was like
that oh we respect you hey you know what
I might not agree with you but I respect
you today
when the Bible tells us the love of many
is waxing cold people are waxing bold
keyboard Warriors people who are hiding
behind all kinds of us are waxing bold
and not even fearing God anymore to the
point where yeah they could be I mean
you would almost think that they they'll
start throwing signs to the pastor and
I'm not talking about peace signs either
that's how bold Satan that's how that's
how bold Satan is and y'all gotta
understand
Satan is doing this because he's trying
to get
Christians to a place where they can
become so angry and so jilted at what
the world is doing that when they get
power oh it's on wait till we get power
y'all haven't seen persecution yet
the devil is using the world to make
Christians angry and in making
Christians angry they are losing
they're losing their minds
they're losing the oil
and you can see it and feel it and sense
it
and then when you speak about it
Pastor you're getting political
talking about injustices in the world
and what Christians ought to do is
political
since when
y'all helped me understand since when
since when listen listen here's the
Three Angels messages here's the first
Angel's message I saw another angel fly
in the midst of Heaven having to
Everlasting lasting gospel to preach
unto them that dwell on the earth and to
Every Nation Kendra tongue and people
same with a loud voice fear God and give
glory to him how do you give glory to
God Matthew 5 14. the Bible says you are
the light of the world a city set on a
hill cannot be hid neither do men light
a candle and put it under a bushel but
on a Candlestick that it gives light to
all that are in the house let your light
so shine before men that they may see
your good works and glorify your father
which is in heaven how are you going to
give glory to God when you're not
allowing good works when you're not
allowing yourself to be woke
spiritually so that you know ah the
devil's just trying to get me mad the
devil's just trying to make me get me to
hate my enemy when I should love my
enemy so how are you going to give glory
to God
when you're not glorifying him in your
character
when you are allowing anger and hatred
to seep into your very veins to where
you even talk to pastors with no respect
and look I'm nobody
I'm not using oh he's a pastor so no you
know I don't care about that
what I'm saying is Satan is elevating
this thing to a level where Christians
are losing common decency to the point
that they are now laughing and mocking
people
who are in Dire Straits
this is stunning stuff y'all
this is stunning stuff
Malachi 3 5 says this I will come near
to you to judgment and I will be a swift
witness against the sorcerers and
against the adulterers and against false
swearers and against those that oppress
the hireling in his wages
the Widow and the fatherless and that
turn aside the stranger that turn aside
the stranger that turn aside the
stranger from his right and fear me not
you see what God says is fear
he says when you
when you turn away the stranger
you're demonstrating that you don't fear
me you cannot give the Three Angels
messages while not fearing God you can't
do it so many of you out there talking
about let's preachers just preach Three
Angels messages we don't care about that
stuff and we don't care about these
injustices really you're not fearing God
you are not fearing God
yes the gospel is not to be filtered
through politics beloved politics is to
be filtered through the gospel for the
Christian but for so many of us Caesar
takes precedence and God comes in second
place I have heard I have heard people
rework
prophecy
through political lenses stuff that's
not in the Bible
man
come on we're almost there we're almost
there guys listen
the Bible says in Isaiah 29 9 stay
yourselves and wonder cry you out and
cry you they are drunken but not with
wine they stagger but not with strong
drink for the Lord has poured out upon
you the spirit of deep sleep you're not
woke you are anti-woke
and proud about it
proud about it
why
those who are drunk fall asleep
could it be that we're drinking the wine
of Babylon
could it be that we are imbibing in
false
Evangelical teachings that don't belong
to us that we've embrace them and that
this this type of ecumenism has entered
into God's people
where what they think is prophecy we now
think is prophecy
and we've fallen asleep to what the
Everlasting gospel really is
come let me show you let me show you I'm
gonna do this I'm gonna do listen
there's a second Parable in Matthew 25.
it goes on verse 14. for the Kingdom of
Heaven is as a man traveling into a far
country who called his own servants and
delivered unto them his Goods hold on a
second y'all
let me ask you a question
who was the here here
who is who is
the man traveling into the far country
just put it in the chat who was the man
in this second Parable who is the man
traveling into the far country y'all
need to hear this if you miss everything
else you need to hear this
you need to hear this
yeah yeah yeah you can call me a dog but
you're not gonna call me a dumb dog I'll
be yes Lord dogs I'm a dog
but I'm a barking dog I'm not gonna be a
dumb dog listen listen
that's Jesus right that's the man that's
gone into the far country
so the question is
that he leaves with his servants
what are the goods and leads of the
servants let's go back to the screen and
I need you to see this what are the
goods that word Goods it means property
or possession
so Jesus goes into a far country and he
leaves his property and his possession
with his servants
okay well what is that let's go to
another Parable very quickly
in Luke 11 when a strong man armed
keepeth his Palace
that's his property
his goods are in peace
but when a stronger than he shall come
upon him and overcome him he take it
from him all his armor when he trusted
and divides his spoils all right
let's break this down real quick
what are the goods in that second
parable
first of all who's the who's the the
strong man in the parable
let me break it down for you very
quickly the strong man is Satan
and his Palace is this world
and the goods are the people
put that in the chat y'all according to
this Parable the goods are the people
then Jesus says but when a stronger than
he comes upon him so who was the wrong
the one stronger than than Satan
come on y'all who is the one stronger
than Satan
the one stronger than Satan is Jesus
yes I see you the one stronger than
Satan is Jesus so when Jesus comes upon
Satan and overcomes him he takes his
possession from him that means this
world is now my world
[Music]
yes yes yes this world is not my world
and and the people in it are my goods
look at what the text says in Roman five
six for when we were yet without
Strength In Due Time Christ died for the
ungodly for scarcely for a righteous man
on one die yet per adventure for a good
man with some even dare to die but God
commended his love toward us in that ra
we were yet sinners Christ died for us
while we were yet sinners Christ died
for us so watch this beloved at the
cross Jesus Takes the possession of the
strong man and now his spoils the goods
are the people now let me ask you a
question put a one in the town if that
makes sense
these Goods
are they righteous people or are they
Wicked people
the goods that now belong to Jesus
are they righteous people
or are they Wicked people
it's everybody all
it's everybody
Jesus says this world I've taken it from
Satan at the cross it now belongs to me
what does that mean the world is his
they're his Goods
the atheists are his they are his Goods
the LGBT community are his they are his
Goods the Democrats are his they are his
Goods the Republicans are his they are
his Goods the immigrants are his they
are his Goods the murderers are his they
are his Goods so what he's saying is
look my servants I'm giving you my goods
to take care of
are y'all catching this
so in this second Parable watch let's go
back to the screen in this second
Parable the the the the man goes away
he's gone to heaven
and he leaves his Goods with his
servants now what do you think he wants
his servants to do with those goods
watch this y'all he gives the servant
something else
Matthew 25 15 and unto one he gave five
talents and to another two and to
another one every man according to his
several ability and straightway took his
journey he pours out the spirit y'all
not feeling me y'all are not feeling me
right now
he pours out his spirit and says all
right I'm gone I'm giving you the fruit
of the spirit what yes Lynn that now
Lynnette why are you stealing my thunder
foreign
why are you stealing my thunder remember
remember God wants these servants to
multiply to be fruitful and multiply
remember what he told them back in
Genesis remember when he told Adam and
Eve back in Genesis
I put you on this Earth to be fruitful
and multiply
what in a spiritual sense God says to
his servants be fruitful and multiply
so beloved what God is expecting from
his servants is that they're going to be
Soul winners
come come
what are these talents
Revelation 13 8 tells us what the
currency of Heaven is
I counsel thee Dubai of me gold tried in
the fire well what is gold in the
scriptures that the trial of your faith
being much more precious than of gold
that parasit though it be tried with
fire it might be found onto praise and
honor and Glory at the appearing of
Jesus Christ so gold is Faith but Faith
doesn't work by itself the Bible tells
us that Faith Works by love listen to me
y'all the currency of Heaven is love
so he says to the servants those who
claim to follow him hey
I'm going to give you my currency
there are my goods now I want you to go
to work and so you know what happens
watch this watch this look at this man
so the one with the five the Bible says
in verse 16 then he that had received
the five talents went and traded
went and traded with the same now what
does that mean trade
come on guys what is he doing when he's
trading what is he doing
come on y'all wake up
he's Trading
we call that like a day job right I'm a
Trader
not traitor but traitor
he's exchanging he's trading he's
working look look
First Peter chapter 3 verse one the same
word for trade is the word one that's
highlighted likewise women being
subjection to your own men that if any
obey not the word they also May without
the word be one by the conversation of
the women
SO trading means winning
how about this the same word is used for
gain in these verses for though I be
free from all men yet have I made myself
servant unto all that I might gain the
more
and unto the Jews I became a Jew that I
might gain trade go to work
for the Jew
to death that are under the law as under
the law that I might gain them that are
under the law so beloved listen in
essence what God is trying to tell us is
that these Servants of his are supposed
to be going to work gaining now you
remember what happens right the five
went out and gained five more
the one with two went out and gained two
more
but the one with one
the one with one
hid his talent
he wasn't a soul winner
he didn't have oil
look at what the text says
take from that Talent from him why
because he buried it and give it unto
him that has the ten talents for enter
foreign to everyone that shall be given
he shall have abundance but for him that
has not it shall be taken away away even
that which he has and can't see out the
unprofitable servant into outer Darkness
now why does Jesus call him unprofitable
listen Cherise think of the talent as
the money the currency of Heaven which
is love what did this guy with the one
Talent do he minded his own business I
like that John Coleman he minded his own
business he did not use love the
currency of Heaven to win others he had
no love
he didn't care about others
let's go back to that other Parable when
a strong man armed king of this Palace
his goods are in peace but when a
stronger than he should come upon him
and overcome him he taketh away from his
honest armor where he trusted and
divided his spoils look at the very next
verse he that is not with me
is against me and he that gathereth not
with me scattereth
come on y'all
if you're not Gathering through the love
of Jesus you are scattering people from
Jesus
if if the love of God is not in you to
love people that you don't agree with to
be kind at all times
to be loving at all times
to love your neighbor
regardless of who they are or where they
come from
then you are scattering abroad and
beloved let me tell you something right
now Christianity as a whole is doing a
whole lot of scattering because
mainstream Christianity has become the
ugliest thing on the planet
easily hands down and how dare we as
God's people Embrace that ugliness
how dare we
Christianity right now is doing so much
scattering there are so many people who
are like I want nothing don't open your
mouth to me about God
cause I see how your Christians do I see
what you're doing in the news I see how
you're reacting I see your callous
attitude I see you cheering this stuff
on I see you excusing pure unadulterated
wickedness
and y'all want me to believe that God is
love
and mercy and Justice and Truth
take that somewhere else
and how dare we as God's Remnant Church
Embrace that foolishness
because that's what it is how dare we
what in the world are you thinking wake
up
wake up
cry aloud spare not wake up
show my people their transgressions
that's Isaiah 58
so you want to know the last Parable I'm
not gonna comment on it I'm just gonna
read it so watch this the first Parable
the five wise and the five foolish
they have no oil the second Parable
right after it same chapter I gave you
talents to take care of my goods and you
did not
the last Parable here it is here it is
no comment really necessary
verse 31 of Matthew 25 when the son of
man shall come in his glory so watch
this oh man
wow
in the first parable
the son of man is away they're waiting
for the bridegroom to come
in the second Parable while he's away
I've given you my talents I've given you
the talents to take care of my goods
now the last Parable the son of man
comes
come on y'all
come on
come on how dare how dare we
I've been in this church for 24 years
I've never seen craziness like this
how dare we begin to use
Evangelical
standards
to determine
who is righteous and who is not
you got a mask on
you must be preparing for the mark of
the beast what kind of what
foreign
can we return to the Bible
and the spirit of Prophecy
can we do that
can we just go back to to the way things
used to be
can we just
can we just go back to our unadulterated
message
without this new political Evangelical
the global Elites can we can we just can
we get back to what we used to preach
because I miss it
I really do
I do I do look look at what the text
says when the son of man shall come in
his glory and all the Holy Angels with
him then shall he sit upon the throne of
his glory and before him shall be
gathered all nations and he shall
separate them one from another as a
Shepherd divided divided his sheep from
the goals the wise from the foolish the
talent the profitable from the
unprofitable
and he shall set the wise on the right
hand and the foolish on the left he
shall set the profitable on the right
hand and the unprofitable on the left he
shall set the Sheep on the right hand
and the goats on the left then shall the
king say unto them on his right hand to
the wise to the profitable Come Ye
blessed my father inherit the Kingdom
prepare for you from the foundation of
the world why wise why uh uh profitable
why sheep four
I was hungry and you gave me meat I was
thirsty and you gave me drink I was a
stranger and you took me in naked and
you clothed me I was sick and you
visited me I was in prison and you came
unto me you had Oil In Your Vessel you
tried you you invested and doubled my
money
that's right y'all when Jesus come comes
back he's gonna ask where's my money
where are my goods
oh you know what I scattered them
because we were in a culture war and you
know I had to let them know that they're
Wicked and I'm righteous
and I also had to Virtue signal to my
own people to let them know huh yeah
that's right
they're Wicked and we're righteous
that's a virtue signal that I stood with
thank you
then saw the righteous answers saying
Lord when saw we thee hungry and said
thee or thirsty and gave thee drink when
sorry be a stranger and took the end or
naked and clothe you or when saw me
these sick or in prison and came unto
thee and the King shall answer and say
unto them verily I say unto you inasmuch
as you did it unto the least of these my
breath and you've done it unto me see
y'all don't understand we don't
understand that that the way that we
treat the person that we like least is
the way that we're treating God
when you don't have the decency
of treating a human with common decency
and respect and not laughing at their
plight
you know how how low that is to laugh at
another person's plight
and then he's going to say to the wicked
then he's going to say to the wicked
depart
then Charlie say unto them on the left
hand
the foolish
those that didn't invest but scattered
depart from me you cursed into
Everlasting fire prepared for the devil
in his angels for I was hungry and you
gave me no drink I was thirsty and you
gave me no I was hungry you gave me no
meat I was thirsty you gave me no drink
I was a stranger you took me out in
naked and you called me not sick and in
prison and you visited me not then shall
they say unto him Lord when saw we thee
hungry and thirsty or stranger a
stranger a stranger an immigrant an
immigrant when saw we thee
and did not Minister unto thee then
shall he answer them and saying verily I
sent to you and as much as you did it
not unto the least of these now who are
these they're his Goods those were my
goods and because of your negligence
because of your negligence because of
your scattering I've lost those goods so
somebody's gonna have to pay for those
goods somebody's gonna have to pay for
all the people who never turn to Jesus
because of the wickedness
of those who profess to serve God
where's my money
where's my investment
no you didn't do it you scattered
these shall go away into Everlasting
punishment but the righteous into
everlasting life so let me just show you
something last two things and we're done
you know what Everlasting punishment is
it's sleep it's Eternal sleep you will
sleep eternally I didn't catch that yeah
no I don't think y'all caught that I'm
gonna give you a little minute I'm gonna
give you a little minute the wicked
shall sleep forever
the Wicked
the wicked
will be anti-voke
forever
those who are not woke now
and remain on woke
will be on woke for all eternity
the Bible says there is no night in the
Kingdom of Heaven
that means God's people gonna be weak
we're gonna be woke for eternity
so you gotta ask a question do I want to
live life woke or anti-woke
forget about the world's definition
you're either going to be awake to
spiritual righteousness awake to the
suffering of others awake to the fact
that God takes precedence over Caesar or
you're not and if you're not
you want to brag about being anti-woke
and wear that as some badge of honor
we're anti-woke that's right
knock yourself out
literally
wake us up Lord
help us to put you over Caesar
I pray y'all
I pray I don't know who's watching this
and I don't know you know I saw earlier
that there might have been an Atheist or
a couple of atheists on I don't know
there's some Christians maybe of other
denominate I don't know but I'm telling
you listen if you're atheist I'm gonna
tell you right now I understand your
absolute
horror
at what Christianity looks like right
now I understand
I get it you don't have to explain to me
I could probably explain more to you
than you could to me because I can show
you
beloved and I call you beloved even
though you're like I don't believe in
God but you're my beloved I can show you
in the Bible where God foretold this
wickedness that would be pawned off as
Christianity and that it's not true
Christianity so I get it I can tell you
I can show you I'll show you stuff in
the Bible you'll be like what the Bible
says that is going to happen in America
and that Christians are going to lead
out in this in this persecution that is
happening right that that we see on the
verge of happening right now yeah and
the Bible says that's not true
Christianity
and if you're a Christian but from some
other denomination you're like man this
is listen I'm not
hidden I'm not like you know trying to
all I'm saying is listen
we need to reflect the character of
Christ
we need to reflect character of Christ
and you may look around at Christianity
and and even have questions yourself I'm
telling you it's not normal what's
happening right now is not normal it is
not Christianity and and seven-day
Adventist all I got to say to you I love
you but how dare we
how dare we guys
we have been given so much light how
dare we put that light aside for that
which is not me how dare we put that
light aside and start bringing in all
kinds of crazy ridiculous
stupid
foolish
block-headed teachings I know you're
gonna be mad at me you're gonna hate me
more I feel like I'm the most abused
Pastor in adventism right now because
people be coming at me all kinds of ways
but you know what people have like ah
Pastor I'm not supporting you anymore
and you this and do that guess what
that's not going to change a thing
that's not going to change a thing I'm
still gonna do what God's called me to
do
period bottom line
and my love for you yeah I'm talking my
love for you is
so nothing y'all can do no matter how
much you curse me out I'm gonna still be
like that's my brother that's my sister
and uh Lord please
get us on the same page
get us marching design together
all right
that's it
I'm done
I just wanted to say
let's be woke
let's be woke Heavenly Father
wake us up from our slumber
wake us up from our indifference
wake us up to the fact that when we are
asleep we're scattering abroad we're not
gathering with you
Lord one day you're going to come back
and you're going to ask what do you do
with the money I gave you to take care
of my goods you knew we didn't have that
money in and of ourselves to take care
of your goods so you gave us love you
gave us Mercy you gave us joy and peace
because of what you did on the cross you
poured that into us and you said now go
bless others with it and so many of us
are not doing that we have hit it in the
sand
forgive us Lord
help us to go dig back into the ground
and find what you gave us and start
using it to gather instead of scatter
forgive us Lord
help us to be awake
to righteousness
help us to demonstrate to the world what
it really means to be woke
thank you for hearing and answering this
prayer Lord
bless everyone watching today wherever
they are however angry they might be or
however rejoicing they might be
pour your blessings out Lord
and in the end may we all be with you
forever woke forever
this is our prayer in Jesus name amen
amen I want to invite you to please
remember if you would like to be a part
of the Afterglow discussion both for the
Sabbath school and divine service I
think the link has just been put up
um so please join us on uh on altar live
uh and we just Fellowship we we we
praise God and we just share the
blessings that we receive for the day
and so I encourage you join that
remember for those of you who want to
get on the living Mana Church mailing
list just go ahead and text
lmoc to the number eight four let's see
if we can get up on the screen uh eight
four five seven six and you will receive
every announcement that we have
um
so just go ahead and sign up for that
and beloved God bless you
um have a good rest of your Sabbath have
a good rest of your day for those of you
who may not be uh who may not be uh
Adventist God bless you God bless you
and uh we'll see you over in altar live
okay
thank you for worshiping with us today
if this is your first time visiting with
us we invite you to check out our
website at livingmanna.live there you
will learn more about our mission to
reach the world with the Gospel of Jesus
we have exciting live programs
throughout the week covering topics like
physical health mental health prayer
learning how to prove God's existence
and much more if you would like to
support the ministry you can click on
the tithe and offering link on our
website we ask that you continue to pray
for the church as God continues to open
doors for our programming to reach the
world thank you again for your prayers
and your support
foreign